[
  {
    "id": 4501,
    "question": "tomás",
    "answer": "Thomas, Tomas"
  },
  {
    "id": 4502,
    "question": "mexicana",
    "answer": "Mexican"
  },
  {
    "id": 4503,
    "question": "bruja",
    "questionDetails": "La bruja hizo una poción mágica.",
    "answer": "sorceress",
    "answerDetails": "The sorceress brewed a magic potion."
  },
  {
    "id": 4504,
    "question": "mexicanos",
    "answer": "Mexican"
  },
  {
    "id": 4505,
    "question": "bodega",
    "questionDetails": "La escotilla de la bodega está abierta.",
    "answer": "cellar",
    "answerDetails": "The cellar hatch is open."
  },
  {
    "id": 4506,
    "question": "ingeniero",
    "questionDetails": "Un ingeniero de autos.",
    "answer": "engineer",
    "answerDetails": "An engineer of a car."
  },
  {
    "id": 4507,
    "question": "rodríguez",
    "answer": "Rodriguez"
  },
  {
    "id": 4508,
    "question": "videos",
    "questionDetails": "Veo videos, como todo el mundo.",
    "answer": "videos, tapes",
    "answerDetails": "I watch videos, like everyone else."
  },
  {
    "id": 4509,
    "question": "cagar",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Apúrate en el baño! ¡ Tengo que cagar y ya no aguanto!.",
    "answer": "crap",
    "answerDetails": "Hurry up in the bathroom! I have to crap and I can’t wait any longer!."
  },
  {
    "id": 4510,
    "question": "suelte",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que suelte a mi hijo.",
    "answer": "release, drop, loosen",
    "answerDetails": "I want you to release my son."
  },
  {
    "id": 4511,
    "question": "advertí",
    "questionDetails": "Le advertí que no viniera.",
    "answer": "warned",
    "answerDetails": "I warned him not to come."
  },
  {
    "id": 4512,
    "question": "bienes",
    "questionDetails": "China exporta billones de dólares de bienes cada año.",
    "answer": "goods",
    "answerDetails": "China exports billions of dollars’ worth of goods every year."
  },
  {
    "id": 4513,
    "question": "cayeron",
    "questionDetails": "Cayeron de las nubes, por la noche.",
    "answer": "fell, dropped, tumbled",
    "answerDetails": "It fell from the clouds, at night."
  },
  {
    "id": 4514,
    "question": "entregue",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que entregue esto.",
    "answer": "deliver",
    "answerDetails": "I want you to deliver this."
  },
  {
    "id": 4515,
    "question": "cansé",
    "questionDetails": "Me cansé de llevarla.",
    "answer": "tired",
    "answerDetails": "I get tired of it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4516,
    "question": "p",
    "questionDetails": "Mirada de p como este.",
    "answer": "p, Q, fr",
    "answerDetails": "The p’s look like this."
  },
  {
    "id": 4517,
    "question": "construcción",
    "questionDetails": "50.000 más puestos de trabajo van desde la construcción.",
    "answer": "construction",
    "answerDetails": "50,000 more jobs will go from construction."
  },
  {
    "id": 4518,
    "question": "traicionó",
    "questionDetails": "Él es el hombre que te traicionó.",
    "answer": "betrayed",
    "answerDetails": "He is the man who betrayed you."
  },
  {
    "id": 4519,
    "question": "recompensa",
    "questionDetails": "Jeff ofreció una recompensa por recuperar a su perro.",
    "answer": "reward, bounty, recompense",
    "answerDetails": "Jeff offered a reward for the return of his dog."
  },
  {
    "id": 4520,
    "question": "prométeme",
    "questionDetails": "Prométeme que me ayudarás a averiguarlo.",
    "answer": "promise",
    "answerDetails": "Promise me you’ll help me find out."
  },
  {
    "id": 4521,
    "question": "agradecerle",
    "questionDetails": "Debemos agradecerle al tío.",
    "answer": "thank",
    "answerDetails": "We should thank our uncle."
  },
  {
    "id": 4522,
    "question": "homicidio",
    "questionDetails": "No negó dispararle a Will, pero afirma que fue en defensa propia y no homicidio.",
    "answer": "homicide, murder",
    "answerDetails": "He didn’t deny shooting Will, but he claims it was self-defense and not homicide."
  },
  {
    "id": 4523,
    "question": "comentarios",
    "answer": "Guest reviews, comments, opinions"
  },
  {
    "id": 4524,
    "question": "conversar",
    "questionDetails": "Era una persona de amplia cultura, capaz de conversar con facilidad sobre infinidad de temas.",
    "answer": "converse",
    "answerDetails": "She was widely read and could converse on any number of subjects with ease."
  },
  {
    "id": 4525,
    "question": "asqueroso",
    "questionDetails": "Es una fruta con un olor asqueroso, pero parece gustarles en ese país.",
    "answer": "gross, foul, lousy",
    "answerDetails": "It is a gross smelling fruit, but they seem to appreciate it in that country."
  },
  {
    "id": 4526,
    "question": "damas",
    "questionDetails": "¿Preferirías jugar al ajedrez o a las damas?",
    "answer": "checkers",
    "answerDetails": "Would you prefer to play checkers or chess?"
  },
  {
    "id": 4527,
    "question": "presos",
    "questionDetails": "Hasta los presos son tranquilos.",
    "answer": "prisoners, inmates, convicts",
    "answerDetails": "Even the prisoners are quiet."
  },
  {
    "id": 4528,
    "question": "the",
    "questionDetails": "Let’s give the winners a Big Hand!.",
    "answer": "las",
    "answerDetails": "¡Un aplauso Para Las Ganadoras!."
  },
  {
    "id": 4529,
    "question": "rezar",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca aprendiste a rezar.",
    "answer": "pray",
    "answerDetails": "You never learned to pray."
  },
  {
    "id": 4530,
    "question": "crema",
    "questionDetails": "Crema de tomate or.",
    "answer": "cream, crème, lotion",
    "answerDetails": "Cream of tomato/chicken soup."
  },
  {
    "id": 4531,
    "question": "soltero",
    "questionDetails": "El príncipe es uno de los solteros más cotizados de europa.",
    "answer": "bachelor",
    "answerDetails": "The prince is one of Europe’s most eligible bachelors."
  },
  {
    "id": 4532,
    "question": "muestro",
    "questionDetails": "Muestro el poder más grande cuando quiera a.",
    "answer": "show, sampling",
    "answerDetails": "It show the biggest power at any time."
  },
  {
    "id": 4533,
    "question": "pretende",
    "questionDetails": "Pretende que lo sabes y di que sí.",
    "answer": "pretend, aims, intended",
    "answerDetails": "Pretend you do and say yes."
  },
  {
    "id": 4534,
    "question": "invertir",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos que invertir la polaridad de las bobinas de plasma.",
    "answer": "reverse",
    "answerDetails": "We need to reverse polarity on the plasma coils."
  },
  {
    "id": 4535,
    "question": "claros",
    "questionDetails": "No hay más mensajes claros en este mundo.",
    "answer": "clear, clearings, glades",
    "answerDetails": "There are no more clear messages in this world."
  },
  {
    "id": 4536,
    "question": "encargó",
    "questionDetails": "Nuestra espías debe encargó determinar estos.",
    "answer": "commissioned, instructed, entrusted",
    "answerDetails": "Our spies must be commissioned to ascertain these."
  },
  {
    "id": 4537,
    "question": "poderosa",
    "questionDetails": "No muy sofisticada, pero sí muy poderosa.",
    "answer": "powerful, mighty, forceful",
    "answerDetails": "Not very sophisticated, but very powerful."
  },
  {
    "id": 4538,
    "question": "agradecerte",
    "questionDetails": "Tiene que agradecerte por ello.",
    "answer": "thank",
    "answerDetails": "He has you to thank for that."
  },
  {
    "id": 4539,
    "question": "comedor",
    "questionDetails": "Ella celebraba con frecuencia cenas en el comedor de la casa solariega.",
    "answer": "dining hall, eating",
    "answerDetails": "She regularly hosted dinner parties in the estate’s huge dining hall."
  },
  {
    "id": 4540,
    "question": "déjanos",
    "questionDetails": "Jenny, ¡ déjanos conocer a tu nuevo novio!.",
    "answer": "let us",
    "answerDetails": "Jenny, let us meet your new boyfriend!."
  },
  {
    "id": 4541,
    "question": "apetece",
    "questionDetails": "No me apetece la idea un poco.",
    "answer": "fancy, want, craving",
    "answerDetails": "I didn’t fancy the idea a bit."
  },
  {
    "id": 4542,
    "question": "apuesta",
    "questionDetails": "Perdió mucho dinero en su última apuesta.",
    "answer": "bet, gamble, ante",
    "answerDetails": "He lost a lot of money on his last bet."
  },
  {
    "id": 4543,
    "question": "pónganse",
    "questionDetails": "Bien, vamos, chicos, pónganse los abrigos.",
    "answer": "get",
    "answerDetails": "Come on, kids, get your coats on."
  },
  {
    "id": 4544,
    "question": "acepté",
    "questionDetails": "Y yo acepté este principio.",
    "answer": "accepted",
    "answerDetails": "I accepted the principle of it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4545,
    "question": "criatura",
    "questionDetails": "Que criatura tan noble.",
    "answer": "creature",
    "answerDetails": "Such a noble creature."
  },
  {
    "id": 4546,
    "question": "clarito",
    "answer": "Clarita"
  },
  {
    "id": 4547,
    "question": "escondida",
    "questionDetails": "Escondida en tu habitación.",
    "answer": "hidden, stashed, tucked away",
    "answerDetails": "Hidden in your room."
  },
  {
    "id": 4548,
    "question": "merecemos",
    "questionDetails": "Y nos lo merecemos.",
    "answer": "deserve",
    "answerDetails": "And we deserve it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4549,
    "question": "traigas",
    "questionDetails": "Mientras traigas la comida.",
    "answer": "bring",
    "answerDetails": "As long as you bring the food."
  },
  {
    "id": 4550,
    "question": "tragar",
    "answer": "stomach"
  },
  {
    "id": 4551,
    "question": "trajimos",
    "questionDetails": "Trajimos bebidas a la fiesta.",
    "answer": "we brought",
    "answerDetails": "We brought drinks to the party."
  },
  {
    "id": 4552,
    "question": "paguen",
    "questionDetails": "Mientras paguen por todo.",
    "answer": "pay",
    "answerDetails": "As long as you pay for it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4553,
    "question": "administración",
    "questionDetails": "Hoy en día, muchas universidades ofrecen licenciaturas en Administración de Empresas.",
    "answer": "management, administration",
    "answerDetails": "Nowadays, many universities offer degrees in Business Management."
  },
  {
    "id": 4554,
    "question": "pareciera",
    "questionDetails": "Pareciera que hay alguien más aparte de nosotros.",
    "answer": "seems",
    "answerDetails": "There seems to be someone else apart from us."
  },
  {
    "id": 4555,
    "question": "produce",
    "answer": "Produces"
  },
  {
    "id": 4556,
    "question": "necesidades",
    "answer": "business"
  },
  {
    "id": 4557,
    "question": "plantas",
    "questionDetails": "Sin las plantas, no tendríamos la posibilidad de existir en este planeta.",
    "answer": "plant life",
    "answerDetails": "Without plant life, we could never hope to exist on this planet."
  },
  {
    "id": 4558,
    "question": "aceptarlo",
    "questionDetails": "La reacción humana es aceptarlo y adaptarse.",
    "answer": "accept",
    "answerDetails": "The human response is to accept and adapt."
  },
  {
    "id": 4559,
    "question": "técnico",
    "questionDetails": "Un técnico del hospital.",
    "answer": "technician",
    "answerDetails": "Technician at the hospital."
  },
  {
    "id": 4560,
    "question": "venda",
    "questionDetails": "Sus captores le quitaron la venda una vez que lo hubieron atado.",
    "answer": "blindfold",
    "answerDetails": "Once his captors had tied him up, they removed the blindfold."
  },
  {
    "id": 4561,
    "question": "joya",
    "questionDetails": "Me encanta leer sus historias porque están llenas de joyas.",
    "answer": "gem",
    "answerDetails": "I love reading her stories because they are full of gems."
  },
  {
    "id": 4562,
    "question": "sitios",
    "questionDetails": "Esta página muestra la lista de sitios que se aprobaron.",
    "answer": "sites, places, websites",
    "answerDetails": "This page lists the sites that were approved."
  },
  {
    "id": 4563,
    "question": "corbata",
    "questionDetails": "Para eventos formales, normalmente lleva traje y corbata.",
    "answer": "tie",
    "answerDetails": "For formal events, he usually wears a suit and tie."
  },
  {
    "id": 4564,
    "question": "decírmelo",
    "questionDetails": "Tienes que decírmelo ahora mismo.",
    "answer": "tell me",
    "answerDetails": "You need to tell me right now."
  },
  {
    "id": 4565,
    "question": "riendo",
    "questionDetails": "Se miraron a los ojos del otro, riendo.",
    "answer": "laughing, chuckling, laughingly",
    "answerDetails": "They looked into each other’s eyes, laughing."
  },
  {
    "id": 4566,
    "question": "pegué",
    "questionDetails": "Le pegué en la cabeza.",
    "answer": "hit, pasted",
    "answerDetails": "I hit him over the head."
  },
  {
    "id": 4567,
    "question": "refería",
    "questionDetails": "Me refería a las ‘otras’ versiones de nosotros.",
    "answer": "meant, referring, talking about",
    "answerDetails": "I meant the ‘other’ versions of us."
  },
  {
    "id": 4568,
    "question": "toco",
    "questionDetails": "Yo toco a otros para hacerlos sentirse bien.",
    "answer": "touch",
    "answerDetails": "I touch other people to make them feel better."
  },
  {
    "id": 4569,
    "question": "ciudades",
    "questionDetails": "Y las ciudades se abandonan cuando las civilizaciones caen.",
    "answer": "cities, towns",
    "answerDetails": "Cities are usually abandoned when civilisations fall."
  },
  {
    "id": 4570,
    "question": "duerma",
    "questionDetails": "Dile que duerma con un ojo abierto.",
    "answer": "sleep, fall asleep, asleep",
    "answerDetails": "Tell him, sleep with one eye open."
  },
  {
    "id": 4571,
    "question": "abrimos",
    "answer": "Open"
  },
  {
    "id": 4572,
    "question": "mental",
    "questionDetails": "La salud mental es muy importante.",
    "answer": "mental, mentally, mind",
    "answerDetails": "Mental health is so important."
  },
  {
    "id": 4573,
    "question": "comentar",
    "answer": "annotate"
  },
  {
    "id": 4574,
    "question": "realizar",
    "questionDetails": "Finalmente pude realizar el pago del seguro.",
    "answer": "carry out",
    "answerDetails": "I could finally carry out the insurance payment."
  },
  {
    "id": 4575,
    "question": "doloroso",
    "questionDetails": "La cicatriz de su mano izquierda era un recordatorio doloroso de su terrible experiencia.",
    "answer": "painful",
    "answerDetails": "The scar on her left hand was a painful reminder of her ordeal."
  },
  {
    "id": 4576,
    "question": "vigilar",
    "questionDetails": "Tendrás que vigilar tu peso si sigues trabajando en esa pastelería.",
    "answer": "watch, police",
    "answerDetails": "You’ll need to watch your weight if you go on working at that cake shop."
  },
  {
    "id": 4577,
    "question": "generar",
    "questionDetails": "Pero el que llevo adentro puede generar miles más.",
    "answer": "generate",
    "answerDetails": "But the one inside of me can generate thousands more."
  },
  {
    "id": 4578,
    "question": "herramientas",
    "questionDetails": "Creo que me he traído todas las herramientas que necesito para arreglarte el ordenador.",
    "answer": "equipment",
    "answerDetails": "I think I have brought with me all the equipment I need to fix your computer."
  },
  {
    "id": 4579,
    "question": "sueltes",
    "questionDetails": "Dije que la sueltes.",
    "answer": "drop",
    "answerDetails": "I told you to drop it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4580,
    "question": "considera",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando considera lo que han conseguido sus hijos, se siente orgulloso.",
    "answer": "he looks at",
    "answerDetails": "When he looks at what his children have all achieved, he feels a sense of pride."
  },
  {
    "id": 4581,
    "question": "normales",
    "questionDetails": "Tiroides normales, no es hepatitis.",
    "answer": "normal, regular, ordinary",
    "answerDetails": "Normal thyroid means no hepatitis."
  },
  {
    "id": 4582,
    "question": "mañanas",
    "questionDetails": "Siempre tomo una copa en las mañanas.",
    "answer": "morning, tomorrows",
    "answerDetails": "I always take a glass in the morning."
  },
  {
    "id": 4583,
    "question": "podrido",
    "questionDetails": "Solíamos enviarle algo podrido.",
    "answer": "rotten, rotting",
    "answerDetails": "We used to send him up something rotten."
  },
  {
    "id": 4584,
    "question": "conforme",
    "questionDetails": "Conforme a tus instrucciones, pintamos la casa de rojo.",
    "answer": "compliance, agreed",
    "answerDetails": "In compliance with your instructions, we painted the house red."
  },
  {
    "id": 4585,
    "question": "hablaban",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando tus tíos estaban vivos, hablaban constantemente.",
    "answer": "they talked",
    "answerDetails": "When your uncles were alive, they talked constantly."
  },
  {
    "id": 4586,
    "question": "entorno",
    "questionDetails": "Esta parte del libro describe el entorno del cuento.",
    "answer": "setting, surroundings",
    "answerDetails": "This part of the book describes the setting of the story."
  },
  {
    "id": 4587,
    "question": "crece",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo entonces, realmente crece en ti.",
    "answer": "grows, grow up",
    "answerDetails": "Only then, does it truly grows in you."
  },
  {
    "id": 4588,
    "question": "acababa",
    "questionDetails": "Yo acababa de encontrar esa cinta.",
    "answer": "just, ended up",
    "answerDetails": "I just found that tape."
  },
  {
    "id": 4589,
    "question": "enseña",
    "questionDetails": "Doug está orgulloso de su colección de sellos y se los enseña a todos sus amigos.",
    "answer": "he shows",
    "answerDetails": "Doug is proud of his stamp collection, and he shows them to all of his friends."
  },
  {
    "id": 4590,
    "question": "acordaba",
    "questionDetails": "Durante el juicio se acordaba.",
    "answer": "remembered",
    "answerDetails": "He remembered them correctly in court."
  },
  {
    "id": 4591,
    "question": "castillo",
    "questionDetails": "El castillo tiene 2 torres y un foso que lo rodea.",
    "answer": "castle",
    "answerDetails": "The castle has two towers and is surrounded by a moat."
  },
  {
    "id": 4592,
    "question": "cuénteme",
    "questionDetails": "Pase a mi oficina, cuénteme todo.",
    "answer": "tell me",
    "answerDetails": "Come to my office and tell me all about it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4593,
    "question": "concha",
    "questionDetails": "El sonido de la concha que pasa, seguido por la explosión.",
    "answer": "shell",
    "answerDetails": "The sound of the shell passing over, followed by the explosion."
  },
  {
    "id": 4594,
    "question": "carajos",
    "answer": "Damn"
  },
  {
    "id": 4595,
    "question": "cantante",
    "answer": "singing"
  },
  {
    "id": 4596,
    "question": "bendiga",
    "questionDetails": "Los bendiga a todos por haberme permitido vivir.",
    "answer": "bless, blessings",
    "answerDetails": "Bless you all for permitting me to live it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4597,
    "question": "leal",
    "questionDetails": "Solo los seguidores más leales del candidato votaron en las pasadas elecciones.",
    "answer": "loyal, fair",
    "answerDetails": "Only the most loyal supporters of the candidate voted in the last election."
  },
  {
    "id": 4598,
    "question": "directora",
    "questionDetails": "La directora les dijo a los maestros que debían ser más estrictos en la aplicación de la hora de acostarse.",
    "answer": "headmistress",
    "answerDetails": "The headmistress told the teachers that they needed to be stricter in the enforcement of bedtime."
  },
  {
    "id": 4599,
    "question": "atrapar",
    "questionDetails": "Solía atrapar gusanos y jugar con ellos.",
    "answer": "catch",
    "answerDetails": "I used to catch worms and play with them."
  },
  {
    "id": 4600,
    "question": "chile",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo le puse un Chile a la sopa para que no estuviera demasiado picante.",
    "answer": "chili",
    "answerDetails": "I only added one chili to the soup so it wouldn’t be too spicy."
  },
  {
    "id": 4601,
    "question": "isla",
    "questionDetails": "La isla de Man.",
    "answer": "isle",
    "answerDetails": "The Isle of Man."
  },
  {
    "id": 4602,
    "question": "jodiendo",
    "questionDetails": "Eso apesta a ti jodiendo con la gente.",
    "answer": "screwing, kidding, kidding me",
    "answerDetails": "It just reeks of you screwing with people."
  },
  {
    "id": 4603,
    "question": "tranquilas",
    "questionDetails": "Se quedaron tranquilas, sus mandíbulas de trabajo.",
    "answer": "quiet, calm, tranquil",
    "answerDetails": "They stood quiet, their jaws working."
  },
  {
    "id": 4604,
    "question": "cagada",
    "questionDetails": "Traes el parabrisas lleno de cagadas de paloma.",
    "answer": "crap",
    "answerDetails": "Your windshield is covered in pigeon crap."
  },
  {
    "id": 4605,
    "question": "párate",
    "questionDetails": "Párate junto a la puerta.",
    "answer": "stand",
    "answerDetails": "Stand against the door."
  },
  {
    "id": 4606,
    "question": "escondiendo",
    "questionDetails": "Debes estas escondiendo algo.",
    "answer": "hiding, hidin’, stashing",
    "answerDetails": "You must be hiding something."
  },
  {
    "id": 4607,
    "question": "debiste",
    "questionDetails": "Le debiste de dar su lugar.",
    "answer": "should",
    "answerDetails": "You should give it to her instead."
  },
  {
    "id": 4608,
    "question": "incendio",
    "questionDetails": "El incendio se descontroló y se quemaron 2 fábricas cercanas.",
    "answer": "fire, blaze",
    "answerDetails": "The fire got out of control and burned two nearby factories."
  },
  {
    "id": 4609,
    "question": "servirle",
    "questionDetails": "Si desea servirle, baje la bandera …",
    "answer": "serve",
    "answerDetails": "If you wish to serve it, take down that flag …"
  },
  {
    "id": 4610,
    "question": "traicionar",
    "questionDetails": "No debo traicionar esa confianza.",
    "answer": "betray",
    "answerDetails": "I must not betray that trust."
  },
  {
    "id": 4611,
    "question": "acompáñeme",
    "answer": "Join me"
  },
  {
    "id": 4612,
    "question": "agradecida",
    "questionDetails": "Te estaré eternamente agradecida.",
    "answer": "grateful, thankful, appreciative",
    "answerDetails": "I will be eternally grateful to you."
  },
  {
    "id": 4613,
    "question": "suéltalo",
    "answer": "Release it"
  },
  {
    "id": 4614,
    "question": "limón",
    "questionDetails": "Y té con limón.",
    "answer": "lemon",
    "answerDetails": "And tea with lemon."
  },
  {
    "id": 4615,
    "question": "confundida",
    "questionDetails": "Pero quizás solo estaba confundida en este nuevo ambiente.",
    "answer": "confused, confounded, mistaken",
    "answerDetails": "But maybe she’s just confused in this new environment."
  },
  {
    "id": 4616,
    "question": "andamos",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando nosotros andamos en caminos de pecado.",
    "answer": "walk",
    "answerDetails": "When we walk on roads of sin."
  },
  {
    "id": 4617,
    "question": "raya",
    "questionDetails": "Las cebras tienen rayas blancas y negras.",
    "answer": "stripe, streak, ray",
    "answerDetails": "Zebras have black and white stripes."
  },
  {
    "id": 4618,
    "question": "sospechar",
    "questionDetails": "Si el doble se cae, todos empezarán a sospechar.",
    "answer": "suspect",
    "answerDetails": "If the double faIls off, everyone will suspect."
  },
  {
    "id": 4619,
    "question": "casarte",
    "questionDetails": "Puedes casarte con quien quieras.",
    "answer": "marry, get married",
    "answerDetails": "You can marry anybody you like."
  },
  {
    "id": 4620,
    "question": "asustada",
    "questionDetails": "Yo estaba más asustada de eso.",
    "answer": "scared, frightened, afraid",
    "answerDetails": "I was more scared of that."
  },
  {
    "id": 4621,
    "question": "reto",
    "questionDetails": "El espadachín aceptó el reto de su rival.",
    "answer": "challenge, dare",
    "answerDetails": "The swordsman took up his rival’s challenge."
  },
  {
    "id": 4622,
    "question": "deseos",
    "questionDetails": "Brisas amistosas, ayuden los deseos de los buenos corazones.",
    "answer": "desires, wishes, lusts",
    "answerDetails": "Friendly breezes, favor the desires of such good hearts."
  },
  {
    "id": 4623,
    "question": "cristo",
    "answer": "Christ"
  },
  {
    "id": 4624,
    "question": "oreja",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Caramba! ¡ Mira qué orejas más grandes tiene!.",
    "answer": "lug",
    "answerDetails": "Blimey, look at the size of those lugs!."
  },
  {
    "id": 4625,
    "question": "injusticia",
    "questionDetails": "Lo que te hicieron fue una injusticia papá.",
    "answer": "injustice",
    "answerDetails": "What they did to you was an injustice, dad."
  },
  {
    "id": 4626,
    "question": "actividades",
    "questionDetails": "Tienen actividades excelentes para los aspirantes.",
    "answer": "activities, efforts",
    "answerDetails": "They have great activities for prospective freshmen."
  },
  {
    "id": 4627,
    "question": "estuviéramos",
    "questionDetails": "Como si estuviéramos malditos.",
    "answer": "were",
    "answerDetails": "As if it were cursed."
  },
  {
    "id": 4628,
    "question": "desgraciadamente",
    "questionDetails": "Desgraciadamente, murieron en el accidente.",
    "answer": "unfortunately, sadly",
    "answerDetails": "Unfortunately, they died in the accident."
  },
  {
    "id": 4629,
    "question": "exagerado",
    "questionDetails": "El informe exagerado de ganancias llevó a un aumento injustificado en el precio de las acciones de la compañía.",
    "answer": "inflated",
    "answerDetails": "The inflated earnings report led to an unjustified increase in the company’s stock price."
  },
  {
    "id": 4630,
    "question": "prepare",
    "questionDetails": "Se prepare para moverse.",
    "answer": "prepare, prep",
    "answerDetails": "Prepare to be moved."
  },
  {
    "id": 4631,
    "question": "conste",
    "questionDetails": "conste que encontrar el defensor público …",
    "answer": "record",
    "answerDetails": "record i find the public defender …"
  },
  {
    "id": 4632,
    "question": "equivocando",
    "questionDetails": "Estás equivocando tu amabilidad con debilidad.",
    "answer": "wrong",
    "answerDetails": "You wrong your kindness for weakness."
  },
  {
    "id": 4633,
    "question": "preferido",
    "questionDetails": "La fuerza no es nuestro modo preferido de manejar estas situaciones.",
    "answer": "preferred, favored",
    "answerDetails": "Force is not our preferred way to handle these situations."
  },
  {
    "id": 4634,
    "question": "autobús",
    "questionDetails": "Tomamos el autobús de las 7 am a Santiago de Chile.",
    "answer": "coach, bus",
    "answerDetails": "We took the 7 A.M. coach to Santiago in Chile."
  },
  {
    "id": 4635,
    "question": "celebración",
    "questionDetails": "La celebración de fin de año promete ser espectacular.",
    "answer": "celebration, festivity",
    "answerDetails": "The year-end celebration promises to be spectacular."
  },
  {
    "id": 4636,
    "question": "valga",
    "questionDetails": "Espero que valga la pena.",
    "answer": "worth",
    "answerDetails": "Hope it was worth it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4637,
    "question": "ciudadano",
    "questionDetails": "Todo ciudadano tiene sus derechos.",
    "answer": "citizen",
    "answerDetails": "Every citizen has rights."
  },
  {
    "id": 4638,
    "question": "asesinado",
    "questionDetails": "Yo era el socio del hombre asesinado.",
    "answer": "murdered, killed, assassinated",
    "answerDetails": "I was the murdered man’s partner."
  },
  {
    "id": 4639,
    "question": "ayudara",
    "questionDetails": "Sería una bendición si nos ayudara.",
    "answer": "help",
    "answerDetails": "It will be a blessing if you help us."
  },
  {
    "id": 4640,
    "question": "cultura",
    "questionDetails": "La cultura griega es rica en historia y tradición.",
    "answer": "culture, education, arts",
    "answerDetails": "Greek culture is rich with history and tradition."
  },
  {
    "id": 4641,
    "question": "muevo",
    "questionDetails": "Me muevo más rápido solo.",
    "answer": "move",
    "answerDetails": "I move faster alone."
  },
  {
    "id": 4642,
    "question": "cuidarme",
    "questionDetails": "… están aquí, querían cuidarme.",
    "answer": "take care",
    "answerDetails": "… are here, they wanted to take care."
  },
  {
    "id": 4643,
    "question": "promesas",
    "questionDetails": "Las promesas en el futuro serán aún más impredecibles.",
    "answer": "promises, pledges, vows",
    "answerDetails": "The future promises to be even more unpredictable."
  },
  {
    "id": 4644,
    "question": "salidas",
    "questionDetails": "Cables y salidas del amplificador.",
    "answer": "outputs, exits, departures",
    "answerDetails": "Cables and amplifier outputs."
  },
  {
    "id": 4645,
    "question": "conversaciones",
    "questionDetails": "El propósito de las conversaciones es llegar a un acuerdo sobre el tema nuclear.",
    "answer": "talks",
    "answerDetails": "The purpose of the talks was to come to an agreement over the nuclear issue."
  },
  {
    "id": 4646,
    "question": "recuperación",
    "questionDetails": "Las condiciones climáticas dificultaron la recuperación de los cuerpos de los dos montañeros.",
    "answer": "retrieval, recovery, recuperation",
    "answerDetails": "Weather conditions have hindered the retrieval of the two mountaineers’ bodies."
  },
  {
    "id": 4647,
    "question": "masa",
    "questionDetails": "Una masa de nubarrones anunciaba la llegada de una tormenta.",
    "answer": "mass, body, batter",
    "answerDetails": "A mass of grey clouds announced the coming of a storm."
  },
  {
    "id": 4648,
    "question": "indicado",
    "questionDetails": "Este gel es muy suave, e indicado para todos los tipos de piel.",
    "answer": "suitable",
    "answerDetails": "This gel is very gentle and suitable for all skin types."
  },
  {
    "id": 4649,
    "question": "querrá",
    "questionDetails": "Sé que querrá una taza de café cuando despierte, así que déjeme mostrarle dónde está la cafetera.",
    "answer": "you will want",
    "answerDetails": "I know you will want a cup of coffee when you wake up, so let me show you where the coffee maker is."
  },
  {
    "id": 4650,
    "question": "receta",
    "questionDetails": "No hay una receta para la felicidad.",
    "answer": "recipe",
    "answerDetails": "There is no recipe for happiness."
  },
  {
    "id": 4651,
    "question": "protegido",
    "questionDetails": "Las plantas necesitan un lugar sombreado y protegido en el jardín.",
    "answer": "sheltered",
    "answerDetails": "The plants need a shady, sheltered spot in the garden."
  },
  {
    "id": 4652,
    "question": "sígueme",
    "questionDetails": "Si no sabes el camino, sígueme en el coche.",
    "answer": "follow me",
    "answerDetails": "If you don’t know the way, follow me in the car."
  },
  {
    "id": 4653,
    "question": "reconocimiento",
    "questionDetails": "Los sistemas de identificación pueden incluir el reconocimiento de imágenes y rostros.",
    "answer": "recognition, appreciation, acknowledgment",
    "answerDetails": "Identification systems can include the recognition of images and faces."
  },
  {
    "id": 4654,
    "question": "raíz",
    "questionDetails": "Para poder curarla, necesitamos averiguar cuál es la raíz de la enfermedad.",
    "answer": "root cause",
    "answerDetails": "To be able to cure it, we need to figure out what the root cause of the illness is."
  },
  {
    "id": 4655,
    "question": "pensaría",
    "questionDetails": "Pero la gente pensaría que lo hiciste.",
    "answer": "think",
    "answerDetails": "But people will think you did."
  },
  {
    "id": 4656,
    "question": "principales",
    "questionDetails": "Los motores principales comienzan en cuatro minutos.",
    "answer": "main, major, principal",
    "answerDetails": "Main engines start in four minutes."
  },
  {
    "id": 4657,
    "question": "falleció",
    "answer": "Died"
  },
  {
    "id": 4658,
    "question": "hilo",
    "questionDetails": "Ella puso su aguja y el hilo de distancia.",
    "answer": "thread, wire, strand",
    "answerDetails": "She put her needle and thread away."
  },
  {
    "id": 4659,
    "question": "mínima",
    "questionDetails": "Apunto de cruzar altura mínima de crucero.",
    "answer": "minimum, min, lowest",
    "answerDetails": "About to cross minimum cruise height."
  },
  {
    "id": 4660,
    "question": "bajes",
    "questionDetails": "Será mejor que la bajes, amigo.",
    "answer": "down",
    "answerDetails": "Better put it down then, mate."
  },
  {
    "id": 4661,
    "question": "harán",
    "questionDetails": "Te harán pagar extra para la entrega.",
    "answer": "they will make",
    "answerDetails": "They will make you pay extra for delivery."
  },
  {
    "id": 4662,
    "question": "arreglarlo",
    "questionDetails": "Llama a alguien que venga a arreglarlo.",
    "answer": "fix it",
    "answerDetails": "Call someone to come over and fix it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4663,
    "question": "efectos",
    "questionDetails": "Después de sobrevivir el huracán, todos sus efectos personales cabían en una sola caja.",
    "answer": "effects",
    "answerDetails": "After surviving the hurricane, all his personal effects could fit into one Box."
  },
  {
    "id": 4664,
    "question": "naciste",
    "questionDetails": "Tú que naciste ciego deberías entender la empatía …",
    "answer": "born",
    "answerDetails": "You of all people, born blind should understand empathy …"
  },
  {
    "id": 4665,
    "question": "roba",
    "questionDetails": "Ya sabes, la que roba niños.",
    "answer": "steals, robs",
    "answerDetails": "You know, who steals children."
  },
  {
    "id": 4666,
    "question": "impacto",
    "questionDetails": "En el momento del impacto.",
    "answer": "impact",
    "answerDetails": "On impact."
  },
  {
    "id": 4667,
    "question": "causas",
    "questionDetails": "El héroe de causas perdidas.",
    "answer": "causes, reasons, cases",
    "answerDetails": "The hero of lost causes."
  },
  {
    "id": 4668,
    "question": "ventanas",
    "answer": "Windows"
  },
  {
    "id": 4669,
    "question": "volveremos",
    "questionDetails": "Volveremos con comida para los hambrientos.",
    "answer": "we will return",
    "answerDetails": "We will return with food for the hungry."
  },
  {
    "id": 4670,
    "question": "pisar",
    "questionDetails": "Deberías pisar con cuidado.",
    "answer": "tread",
    "answerDetails": "You should tread carefully."
  },
  {
    "id": 4671,
    "question": "regalado",
    "questionDetails": "Pensé que la habías regalado.",
    "answer": "given, gifted",
    "answerDetails": "I thought you’d given it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4672,
    "question": "neta",
    "questionDetails": "No hay suficiente fuerza neta para alcanzar el levantamiento aerodinámico.",
    "answer": "net",
    "answerDetails": "Not enough net force to achieve aerodynamic lift."
  },
  {
    "id": 4673,
    "question": "pará",
    "answer": "Pará"
  },
  {
    "id": 4674,
    "question": "franco",
    "questionDetails": "El candidato principal es un Franco detractor del sistema público de salud.",
    "answer": "outspoken",
    "answerDetails": "The primary candidate is an outspoken critic of the healthcare system."
  },
  {
    "id": 4675,
    "question": "entendés",
    "questionDetails": "Y además yo siempre le digo,¿entendés?",
    "answer": "understand",
    "answerDetails": "I always tell her, do you understand?"
  },
  {
    "id": 4676,
    "question": "selva",
    "questionDetails": "Política de poder reflejaba la ley de la selva.",
    "answer": "jungle, forest",
    "answerDetails": "Power politics reflected the law of the jungle."
  },
  {
    "id": 4677,
    "question": "sobrina",
    "questionDetails": "Su sobrina no sabía nada de hombres.",
    "answer": "niece",
    "answerDetails": "Your niece knew nothing of such men."
  },
  {
    "id": 4678,
    "question": "candidato",
    "questionDetails": "Ni un solo candidato aceptable.",
    "answer": "candidate",
    "answerDetails": "Not one acceptable candidate."
  },
  {
    "id": 4679,
    "question": "tequila",
    "questionDetails": "Tú hueles a tequila.",
    "answer": "tequila",
    "answerDetails": "You smell like tequila."
  },
  {
    "id": 4680,
    "question": "galán",
    "questionDetails": "Marlon es sólo un empleado de oficina, pero se esfuerza por vestirse siempre como un galán.",
    "answer": "beau",
    "answerDetails": "Marlon is just a clerk in an office, but he strives to always dress like a beau."
  },
  {
    "id": 4681,
    "question": "amiguita",
    "questionDetails": "Esto es todo lo que queda de tu amiguita.",
    "answer": "girlfriend, playmate",
    "answerDetails": "This is all that’s left of your girlfriend."
  },
  {
    "id": 4682,
    "question": "soldados",
    "questionDetails": "Tuvimos que destinar más de 2, 000 soldados al extranjero para ayudar con el esfuerzo bélico.",
    "answer": "troops",
    "answerDetails": "We had to deploy over 2,000 troops abroad to aid in the war effort."
  },
  {
    "id": 4683,
    "question": "espéreme",
    "questionDetails": "Usted solo espéreme aquí en la mesa.",
    "answer": "wait",
    "answerDetails": "You just wait here at the table."
  },
  {
    "id": 4684,
    "question": "gimnasio",
    "questionDetails": "Repito, apoyo al gimnasio.",
    "answer": "gymnasium",
    "answerDetails": "I repeat, backup in the gymnasium!"
  },
  {
    "id": 4685,
    "question": "nieta",
    "questionDetails": "Mi nieta tenía un demonio.",
    "answer": "granddaughter",
    "answerDetails": "My granddaughter had a demon in her."
  },
  {
    "id": 4686,
    "question": "suéltala",
    "questionDetails": "Suéltala y muéstreme sus manos.",
    "answer": "drop",
    "answerDetails": "Drop it and show me your hands."
  },
  {
    "id": 4687,
    "question": "cancha",
    "questionDetails": "Mi complejo residencial tiene una cancha de tenis.",
    "answer": "court",
    "answerDetails": "My apartment complex has a tennis court."
  },
  {
    "id": 4688,
    "question": "pizza",
    "questionDetails": "Gracias por la pizza.",
    "answer": "pizza",
    "answerDetails": "Thanks for the pizza."
  },
  {
    "id": 4689,
    "question": "préstamo",
    "questionDetails": "Pagamos el préstamo bancario antes de la fecha estipulada en el contrato.",
    "answer": "loan",
    "answerDetails": "We repaid the bank loan before the date agreed on in the contract."
  },
  {
    "id": 4690,
    "question": "maquillaje",
    "questionDetails": "Taylor se pone maquillaje todas las mañanas antes de salir de la casa.",
    "answer": "makeup",
    "answerDetails": "Taylor puts her makeup on every morning before leaving the house."
  },
  {
    "id": 4691,
    "question": "armados",
    "questionDetails": "Los sospechosos están probablemente armados y son peligrosos.",
    "answer": "armed, armoured",
    "answerDetails": "Suspects are possibly armed and dangerous."
  },
  {
    "id": 4692,
    "question": "mosca",
    "questionDetails": "Y la vida de una mosca es aún más corta.",
    "answer": "fly",
    "answerDetails": "And the life of a fly is even shorter."
  },
  {
    "id": 4693,
    "question": "fan",
    "answer": "fan"
  },
  {
    "id": 4694,
    "question": "materiales",
    "questionDetails": "Yo deseo pedir los materiales para hacer un testamento.",
    "answer": "materials",
    "answerDetails": "I wish to request materials to make a will."
  },
  {
    "id": 4695,
    "question": "trabaje",
    "answer": "Work"
  },
  {
    "id": 4696,
    "question": "posiblemente",
    "questionDetails": "¿Vas a venir a mi fiesta de cumpleaños?-Posiblemente.",
    "answer": "maybe",
    "answerDetails": "Are you coming to my birthday party?-Maybe."
  },
  {
    "id": 4697,
    "question": "novela",
    "questionDetails": "En su última novela, la autora exploró el feminismo y la sexualidad.",
    "answer": "novel",
    "answerDetails": "In her last novel, the author explored feminism and sexuality."
  },
  {
    "id": 4698,
    "question": "trates",
    "questionDetails": "No trates de librarte de mí.",
    "answer": "try, treat, tryto",
    "answerDetails": "Do not try to weasel out on me."
  },
  {
    "id": 4699,
    "question": "prepárate",
    "questionDetails": "Prepárate, Janet. Nos vamos en 5 minutos.",
    "answer": "get ready",
    "answerDetails": "Get ready, Janet. We’re leaving in five minutes."
  },
  {
    "id": 4700,
    "question": "explosión",
    "questionDetails": "Dio salida a toda su frustración en una explosión de ira.",
    "answer": "explosion, burst",
    "answerDetails": "All her frustration came out in an explosion of anger."
  },
  {
    "id": 4701,
    "question": "extrañas",
    "questionDetails": "Los cuales tienen unas costumbres muy extrañas.",
    "answer": "strange, weird, miss",
    "answerDetails": "And they have some very strange habits."
  },
  {
    "id": 4702,
    "question": "jodida",
    "questionDetails": "Baja tu jodida voz.",
    "answer": "fucking, fucked, fucked up",
    "answerDetails": "Lower your fucking voice."
  },
  {
    "id": 4703,
    "question": "demostrado",
    "questionDetails": "Nosotros hemos demostrado rigor.",
    "answer": "shown, demonstrated, proven",
    "answerDetails": "We have shown rigour."
  },
  {
    "id": 4704,
    "question": "fotografías",
    "questionDetails": "Un panorama trató de componer dos piezas de fotografías.",
    "answer": "photographs, pictures",
    "answerDetails": "A panorama tried to compose two pieces of photographs."
  },
  {
    "id": 4705,
    "question": "adelantar",
    "questionDetails": "En esta carretera no se permite adelantar.",
    "answer": "overtake",
    "answerDetails": "You’re not allowed to overtake on this road."
  },
  {
    "id": 4706,
    "question": "restos",
    "questionDetails": "Después del Día de Acción de Gracias, usamos los restos del pavo para hacer una sopa.",
    "answer": "remains, wreckage, debris",
    "answerDetails": "After Thanksgiving, we use the remains of the turkey to make a soup."
  },
  {
    "id": 4707,
    "question": "entradas",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo entradas para el estreno para todas.",
    "answer": "tickets, entries, inputs",
    "answerDetails": "I got tickets for us all opening night."
  },
  {
    "id": 4708,
    "question": "to",
    "questionDetails": "In order to achieve his aims.",
    "answer": "para, con",
    "answerDetails": "Para conseguir SUS propósitos."
  },
  {
    "id": 4709,
    "question": "opina",
    "questionDetails": "Su doctor opina que usted necesita hacerse una punción lumbar …",
    "answer": "believes, think, feels",
    "answerDetails": "Your doctor believes you need a lumbar puncture or spinal tap …"
  },
  {
    "id": 4710,
    "question": "salte",
    "questionDetails": "Le dijo que salte al agua.",
    "answer": "jump, skip, springing up",
    "answerDetails": "You told her to jump into the water."
  },
  {
    "id": 4711,
    "question": "revistas",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo otra cara vendiendo revistas.",
    "answer": "magazines, journals, revues",
    "answerDetails": "Just another face selling magazines."
  },
  {
    "id": 4712,
    "question": "estable",
    "questionDetails": "Pensé que sería mejor conseguir un trabajo estable.",
    "answer": "steady",
    "answerDetails": "I thought I’d better get a steady job."
  },
  {
    "id": 4713,
    "question": "importó",
    "questionDetails": "A mí nunca me importó.",
    "answer": "mattered, imported, cared about",
    "answerDetails": "I never actually mattered, myself."
  },
  {
    "id": 4714,
    "question": "encuentres",
    "questionDetails": "Espero que encuentres a alguien que encaje.",
    "answer": "find, encounter",
    "answerDetails": "I hope you find someone who fits in."
  },
  {
    "id": 4715,
    "question": "apagado",
    "questionDetails": "Un vestido en tonos apagados de polvo azul y rosa polvoriento.",
    "answer": "muted",
    "answerDetails": "A dress in muted tones of powder blue and dusty pink."
  },
  {
    "id": 4716,
    "question": "copias",
    "questionDetails": "Necesito copias de los cuatro vídeos.",
    "answer": "copies, renditions, backups",
    "answerDetails": "I need copies of all four images."
  },
  {
    "id": 4717,
    "question": "ofrecerle",
    "questionDetails": "Deseo ofrecerle una palabra de consuelo en privado.",
    "answer": "offer",
    "answerDetails": "I wish to offer a word of comfort in private."
  },
  {
    "id": 4718,
    "question": "inocencia",
    "questionDetails": "Me encanta tu inocencia.",
    "answer": "innocence",
    "answerDetails": "I adore your innocence!"
  },
  {
    "id": 4719,
    "question": "bienestar",
    "questionDetails": "Un sistema sanitario centrado en el bienestar, no en la enfermedad.",
    "answer": "wellness, welfare",
    "answerDetails": "A healthcare system focused on wellness, not sickness."
  },
  {
    "id": 4720,
    "question": "equivocó",
    "questionDetails": "Nadie se equivocó en intentar romper la tensión.",
    "answer": "wrong, misspoke, screwed up",
    "answerDetails": "No one ever went wrong breaking the tension."
  },
  {
    "id": 4721,
    "question": "nadar",
    "questionDetails": "Los rusos fueron capaces de nadar sus portaaviones de infantería a través de.",
    "answer": "swim",
    "answerDetails": "The Russians were able to swim their infantry carriers across."
  },
  {
    "id": 4722,
    "question": "raza",
    "questionDetails": "Todos somos miembros de la raza humana sea el que sea el color o credo.",
    "answer": "race, breed",
    "answerDetails": "We’re all members of the human race regardless of color or creed."
  },
  {
    "id": 4723,
    "question": "pegaron",
    "questionDetails": "… limpiaba los gusanos parasitarios que se pegaron a otros peces.",
    "answer": "stuck",
    "answerDetails": "… cleaning the parasitic worms which stuck to other fish."
  },
  {
    "id": 4724,
    "question": "robaste",
    "questionDetails": "Le robaste su dinero.",
    "answer": "stole, robbed, swiped",
    "answerDetails": "You stole their money."
  },
  {
    "id": 4725,
    "question": "compre",
    "answer": "Buy"
  },
  {
    "id": 4726,
    "question": "encerrados",
    "questionDetails": "Me dijeron que los pacientes estaban encerrados en sus celdas.",
    "answer": "locked, enclosed, cooped up",
    "answerDetails": "You told me the patients were locked in their cells."
  },
  {
    "id": 4727,
    "question": "digno",
    "questionDetails": "Consejo digno, pero tedioso.",
    "answer": "worthy, deserving",
    "answerDetails": "Worthy but tedious advice."
  },
  {
    "id": 4728,
    "question": "palos",
    "questionDetails": "El jinete se cayó cuando el caballo golpeó los palos.",
    "answer": "rails",
    "answerDetails": "The rider fell off when his horse hit the rails."
  },
  {
    "id": 4729,
    "question": "reventar",
    "questionDetails": "Comimos casi hasta reventar.",
    "answer": "burst",
    "answerDetails": "And we ate till we nearly burst."
  },
  {
    "id": 4730,
    "question": "cambiaste",
    "questionDetails": "Le cambiaste la vida.",
    "answer": "changed",
    "answerDetails": "You changed her life."
  },
  {
    "id": 4731,
    "question": "cargando",
    "questionDetails": "Están cargando el barco.",
    "answer": "loading, charging, carrying",
    "answerDetails": "The boat is now loading."
  },
  {
    "id": 4732,
    "question": "preparé",
    "questionDetails": "Ya preparé una orden.",
    "answer": "prepared",
    "answerDetails": "I have prepared the order."
  },
  {
    "id": 4733,
    "question": "conductor",
    "questionDetails": "Mi padre es conductor del metro.",
    "answer": "driver",
    "answerDetails": "My father’s a metro driver."
  },
  {
    "id": 4734,
    "question": "convenció",
    "questionDetails": "Y eso nos convenció a todos.",
    "answer": "convinced, persuaded, coaxed",
    "answerDetails": "So that convinced us all."
  },
  {
    "id": 4735,
    "question": "aniversario",
    "questionDetails": "Mas en la víspera de mi aniversario el collar desapareció.",
    "answer": "birthday",
    "answerDetails": "The day before my birthday, the necklace disappeared."
  },
  {
    "id": 4736,
    "question": "fantasía",
    "questionDetails": "No Estoy segura de que Miriam sepa la diferencia entre la realidad y la fantasía.",
    "answer": "fancy, fantasia, fantasy",
    "answerDetails": "I’m not convinced Miriam knows the difference between fact and fancy."
  },
  {
    "id": 4737,
    "question": "perderlo",
    "questionDetails": "Puedo perderlo todo por esto.",
    "answer": "lose",
    "answerDetails": "I could lose everything over this."
  },
  {
    "id": 4738,
    "question": "preguntarme",
    "questionDetails": "Puedes preguntarme lo que quieras.",
    "answer": "ask me",
    "answerDetails": "You can ask me anything you like."
  },
  {
    "id": 4739,
    "question": "triple",
    "questionDetails": "Pero hagámoslo como una integral triple.",
    "answer": "triple, treble, tri",
    "answerDetails": "But let’s do it as a triple integral."
  },
  {
    "id": 4740,
    "question": "sentimental",
    "questionDetails": "Ésa era demasiado tierna y sentimental.",
    "answer": "sentimental, sentimentalist, sappy",
    "answerDetails": "That was so soft and sentimental."
  },
  {
    "id": 4741,
    "question": "apoya",
    "questionDetails": "La población apoya estas medidas.",
    "answer": "supports, endorses, rests",
    "answerDetails": "The public supports these measures."
  },
  {
    "id": 4742,
    "question": "regresen",
    "questionDetails": "Regresen a la estación inmediatamente.",
    "answer": "return, come back",
    "answerDetails": "Return to the station immediately."
  },
  {
    "id": 4743,
    "question": "traerte",
    "questionDetails": "Quise venir personalmente para traerte la noticia.",
    "answer": "bring",
    "answerDetails": "I wanted to come bring the news myself."
  },
  {
    "id": 4744,
    "question": "anuncio",
    "questionDetails": "Va a aparecer en un anuncio para crema de rasurar.",
    "answer": "ad, announcement, notice",
    "answerDetails": "She’s going to appear in an ad for shaving cream."
  },
  {
    "id": 4745,
    "question": "llamara",
    "questionDetails": "Incluso le dijeron que no llamara a su madre.",
    "answer": "call",
    "answerDetails": "They even told him not to call his mother."
  },
  {
    "id": 4746,
    "question": "inventó",
    "answer": "invention"
  },
  {
    "id": 4747,
    "question": "concreto",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo un interés concreto en la ley internacional.",
    "answer": "particular, specific",
    "answerDetails": "I have a particular interest in International Law."
  },
  {
    "id": 4748,
    "question": "seguirá",
    "questionDetails": "Lo seguirá haciendo hasta que alguien lo detenga.",
    "answer": "will",
    "answerDetails": "He will do so until he is stopped."
  },
  {
    "id": 4749,
    "question": "injusta",
    "questionDetails": "La vida es demasiado injusta.",
    "answer": "unfair, unjust, wrongful",
    "answerDetails": "Life is very unfair."
  },
  {
    "id": 4750,
    "question": "reserva",
    "questionDetails": "Reservas.",
    "answer": "reserves, booking, reservation",
    "answerDetails": "Energy reserves."
  },
  {
    "id": 4751,
    "question": "celebrarlo",
    "questionDetails": "Deberíamos salir y celebrarlo.",
    "answer": "celebrate",
    "answerDetails": "We should go out and celebrate."
  },
  {
    "id": 4752,
    "question": "sepamos",
    "questionDetails": "Puede que no sepamos cómo, pero sabemos por qué.",
    "answer": "know",
    "answerDetails": "We may not know how, but we know why."
  },
  {
    "id": 4753,
    "question": "adecuado",
    "questionDetails": "El nuevo presupuesto pretende asegurar niveles adecuados de personal a toda hora.",
    "answer": "appropriate, proper",
    "answerDetails": "The new budget seeks to ensure appropriate staffing levels at all times."
  },
  {
    "id": 4754,
    "question": "olla",
    "questionDetails": "Metió la pasta en la olla de agua.",
    "answer": "pot, cooker, saucepan",
    "answerDetails": "He put the pasta in the pot of water."
  },
  {
    "id": 4755,
    "question": "avanzando",
    "questionDetails": "El enemigo estaba avanzando.",
    "answer": "advancing, moving forward, progressing",
    "answerDetails": "The enemy was advancing."
  },
  {
    "id": 4756,
    "question": "cogí",
    "questionDetails": "Cogí este número de la nada.",
    "answer": "grabbed, took",
    "answerDetails": "I just grabbed this number out of the blue."
  },
  {
    "id": 4757,
    "question": "altas",
    "questionDetails": "Así que tiene amigos en las altas esferas.",
    "answer": "high, tall, upper",
    "answerDetails": "So he’s got friends in high places."
  },
  {
    "id": 4758,
    "question": "seremos",
    "questionDetails": "Ni siquiera seremos mencionados.",
    "answer": "be",
    "answerDetails": "We will not even be mentioned."
  },
  {
    "id": 4759,
    "question": "protege",
    "questionDetails": "Nuestros enemigos creen que les protege un viento divino.",
    "answer": "protects, safeguards, secures",
    "answerDetails": "Our enemies believe that a divine wind protects them."
  },
  {
    "id": 4760,
    "question": "daños",
    "questionDetails": "Encontré daños cerebrales pero no hay golpes en la cabeza.",
    "answer": "damage, harm, injury",
    "answerDetails": "I found brain damage but no bruises on her scalp."
  },
  {
    "id": 4761,
    "question": "paramos",
    "questionDetails": "Nos paramos en una curva.",
    "answer": "stopped, moors",
    "answerDetails": "We stopped on a corner."
  },
  {
    "id": 4762,
    "question": "abres",
    "questionDetails": "Abres las latas de cerveza con los dientes!",
    "answer": "open",
    "answerDetails": "You open beer cans with your teeth!"
  },
  {
    "id": 4763,
    "question": "pudieras",
    "questionDetails": "Quisiera que pudieras verme hoy.",
    "answer": "could",
    "answerDetails": "I wish you could see me tonight."
  },
  {
    "id": 4764,
    "question": "verán",
    "questionDetails": "Los niños disfrutarán el acuario. Verán muchos animales increíbles allí.",
    "answer": "they will see",
    "answerDetails": "The children will enjoy the acquarium. They will see lots of incredible animals there."
  },
  {
    "id": 4765,
    "question": "héroes",
    "questionDetails": "Necesitamos ser héroes como papá.",
    "answer": "heroes",
    "answerDetails": "We need to be heroes like dad."
  },
  {
    "id": 4766,
    "question": "levantado",
    "answer": "Raised"
  },
  {
    "id": 4767,
    "question": "llevará",
    "questionDetails": "Me llevará un par de días terminar el trabajo.",
    "answer": "it will take",
    "answerDetails": "It will take me a couple of days to finish the job."
  },
  {
    "id": 4768,
    "question": "suene",
    "questionDetails": "Hace que suene demasiado simple.",
    "answer": "sound, ring",
    "answerDetails": "You make it sound too simple."
  },
  {
    "id": 4769,
    "question": "bajan",
    "questionDetails": "… las burbujas suben y bajan.",
    "answer": "fall, descend",
    "answerDetails": "… as the bubbles continue to rise and fall."
  },
  {
    "id": 4770,
    "question": "consecuencia",
    "questionDetails": "Como consecuencia.",
    "answer": "consequence, result",
    "answerDetails": "As a consequence."
  },
  {
    "id": 4771,
    "question": "seguiremos",
    "questionDetails": "… nuestras leyes y lo seguiremos haciendo.",
    "answer": "continue",
    "answerDetails": "… our laws and will continue to do so."
  },
  {
    "id": 4772,
    "question": "colocar",
    "questionDetails": "Ella finalmente dijo que no podía colocarlo.",
    "answer": "place",
    "answerDetails": "She eventually said she couldn’t place him."
  },
  {
    "id": 4773,
    "question": "hágale",
    "questionDetails": "Hágale conocer sus sentimientos por él.",
    "answer": "make",
    "answerDetails": "Make your feelings known to him."
  },
  {
    "id": 4774,
    "question": "lucía",
    "answer": "Lucia"
  },
  {
    "id": 4775,
    "question": "decime",
    "questionDetails": "Decime dónde te ibas a encontrar con tus amigos.",
    "answer": "tell me",
    "answerDetails": "Tell me where you were going to meet your friends."
  },
  {
    "id": 4776,
    "question": "pinches",
    "questionDetails": "Conozco las pinches reglas.",
    "answer": "fucking",
    "answerDetails": "I know the fucking rules."
  },
  {
    "id": 4777,
    "question": "muchachas",
    "questionDetails": "Las muchachas están de camino.",
    "answer": "girls, young girls, gals",
    "answerDetails": "The girls are on their way."
  },
  {
    "id": 4778,
    "question": "euros",
    "questionDetails": "Cerca de seis millones de euros.",
    "answer": "euros, EUR, USD",
    "answerDetails": "About six million euros."
  },
  {
    "id": 4779,
    "question": "infeliz",
    "questionDetails": "Parece ser una mujer muy infeliz.",
    "answer": "unhappy",
    "answerDetails": "She seems to be a very unhappy woman."
  },
  {
    "id": 4780,
    "question": "cheque",
    "questionDetails": "Me mandaron un cheque por correo.",
    "answer": "check",
    "answerDetails": "They sent me a check by mail."
  },
  {
    "id": 4781,
    "question": "diablos",
    "questionDetails": "Diablos, otra vez voy a llegar tarde a mi clase de karate.",
    "answer": "heck, bloody hell, dang",
    "answerDetails": "Oh heck, I’m late again for my karate class."
  },
  {
    "id": 4782,
    "question": "helicóptero",
    "questionDetails": "Los helicópteros de la policía permanecían inmóviles sobrevolando el centro de la ciudad.",
    "answer": "chopper, helicopter",
    "answerDetails": "Police choppers hovered over the center of town."
  },
  {
    "id": 4783,
    "question": "gay",
    "questionDetails": "Creo que este tipo es gay.",
    "answer": "gay, queer",
    "answerDetails": "I think this guy’s gay."
  },
  {
    "id": 4784,
    "question": "cuídese",
    "questionDetails": "De acuerdo, cuídese.",
    "answer": "take care",
    "answerDetails": "All right, take care."
  },
  {
    "id": 4785,
    "question": "corrupción",
    "questionDetails": "La palabra ‘ adicto ‘ evoca el mal y la corrupción.",
    "answer": "corruption",
    "answerDetails": "The word ‘addict’ conjures up evil and corruption."
  },
  {
    "id": 4786,
    "question": "cuñada",
    "questionDetails": "y brindo por mi nueva cuñada.",
    "answer": "sister",
    "answerDetails": "And here’s to my new sister."
  },
  {
    "id": 4787,
    "question": "heridos",
    "questionDetails": "Los heridos salieron arrastrándose del autobús destrozado.",
    "answer": "injured",
    "answerDetails": "The injured crawled out of the wrecked bus."
  },
  {
    "id": 4788,
    "question": "ocultando",
    "questionDetails": "Creo que están todos ocultando algo.",
    "answer": "hiding, concealing, withholding",
    "answerDetails": "I think they’re all hiding something."
  },
  {
    "id": 4789,
    "question": "sentencia",
    "questionDetails": "Está previsto que dicte sentencia sobre el caso mañana.",
    "answer": "judgment, sentence, decision",
    "answerDetails": "He is due to pass judgment on the case tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "id": 4790,
    "question": "cañón",
    "questionDetails": "El granjero les metió el cañón de la escopeta en la cara.",
    "answer": "barrel",
    "answerDetails": "The farmer thrust the barrel of the shotgun in their faces."
  },
  {
    "id": 4791,
    "question": "casó",
    "questionDetails": "También se casó con un chico estupendo.",
    "answer": "married, wed",
    "answerDetails": "A really nice guy married me."
  },
  {
    "id": 4792,
    "question": "dolió",
    "questionDetails": "Eso parece que dolió.",
    "answer": "hurt, grieved",
    "answerDetails": "That looked like it hurt."
  },
  {
    "id": 4793,
    "question": "échale",
    "questionDetails": "Échale una mirada a esto.",
    "answer": "take",
    "answerDetails": "Take a look at this."
  },
  {
    "id": 4794,
    "question": "inconveniente",
    "questionDetails": "El único inconveniente de mi apartamento en Nueva York era que no tenía bañera.",
    "answer": "drawback, inconvenient, downside",
    "answerDetails": "The only drawback to my apartment in New York was it had no bathtub."
  },
  {
    "id": 4795,
    "question": "explicarle",
    "questionDetails": "Déjeme explicarle de dónde venimos.",
    "answer": "explain",
    "answerDetails": "I should explain where we come from."
  },
  {
    "id": 4796,
    "question": "invitada",
    "questionDetails": "Saludo a nuestra invitada con palabras de bienvenida.",
    "answer": "guest",
    "answerDetails": "Greet our guest with words of welcome."
  },
  {
    "id": 4797,
    "question": "cuernos",
    "questionDetails": "Y éstos son los cuernos.",
    "answer": "horns, horned, antlers",
    "answerDetails": "And these are the horns."
  },
  {
    "id": 4798,
    "question": "amaba",
    "questionDetails": "Amaba su trabajo y le dedicó su vida.",
    "answer": "she loved, he loved her",
    "answerDetails": "She loved her work and dedicated her life to it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4799,
    "question": "españoles",
    "questionDetails": "Los barcos españoles suelen ser lentos.",
    "answer": "spanish",
    "answerDetails": "Spanish ships are notoriously slow."
  },
  {
    "id": 4800,
    "question": "suicidio",
    "questionDetails": "Sufría de depresión e incluso había considerado el suicidio.",
    "answer": "suicide",
    "answerDetails": "I was suffering from depression and had even contemplated suicide."
  },
  {
    "id": 4801,
    "question": "compañeras",
    "questionDetails": "Vamos, bellas compañeras.",
    "answer": "companions, roommates, teammates",
    "answerDetails": "Let us go, gracious companions."
  },
  {
    "id": 4802,
    "question": "permites",
    "questionDetails": "Pero nunca permites a la energía ser pura.",
    "answer": "allow",
    "answerDetails": "But you never allow energy to be pure."
  },
  {
    "id": 4803,
    "question": "eches",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que le eches un vistazo.",
    "answer": "take",
    "answerDetails": "I want you to take a look."
  },
  {
    "id": 4804,
    "question": "vaca",
    "questionDetails": "Atravesamos un campo lleno de vacas.",
    "answer": "cow, beef",
    "answerDetails": "We walked across a field full of cows."
  },
  {
    "id": 4805,
    "question": "envío",
    "questionDetails": "Un envío acelerado cuesta más.",
    "answer": "shipping, consignment, shipment",
    "answerDetails": "Priority shipping will cost extra."
  },
  {
    "id": 4806,
    "question": "obligar",
    "questionDetails": "Obligar a alguien a hacer algo.",
    "answer": "compel",
    "answerDetails": "To compel somebody to do something."
  },
  {
    "id": 4807,
    "question": "publicidad",
    "questionDetails": "A pesar de ser instruido a tomar las señales hacia abajo, dice que no tiene intención de eliminar la publicidad.",
    "answer": "advertising, publicity, promotion",
    "answerDetails": "Despite being instructed to take the signs down, he says he has no intention of removing the advertising."
  },
  {
    "id": 4808,
    "question": "generoso",
    "questionDetails": "Un generoso benefactor de la Universidad.",
    "answer": "generous",
    "answerDetails": "A generous benefactor to the University."
  },
  {
    "id": 4809,
    "question": "cuadras",
    "questionDetails": "Pensé que podríamos caminar unas pocas cuadras.",
    "answer": "blocks, stables, streets",
    "answerDetails": "I thought we’d just walk a few blocks."
  },
  {
    "id": 4810,
    "question": "look",
    "questionDetails": "Me gusta el nuevo look del sitio.",
    "answer": "look, outfit",
    "answerDetails": "I like the new look of the place."
  },
  {
    "id": 4811,
    "question": "largar",
    "answer": "leave"
  },
  {
    "id": 4812,
    "question": "placa",
    "questionDetails": "La placa del Océano Pacífico.",
    "answer": "plate, board, badge",
    "answerDetails": "The Pacific Ocean plate."
  },
  {
    "id": 4813,
    "question": "convencida",
    "questionDetails": "Estaba convencida de que había atropellado a alguien.",
    "answer": "convinced, persuaded",
    "answerDetails": "She was convinced that she had run someone over."
  },
  {
    "id": 4814,
    "question": "incómodo",
    "questionDetails": "Es incómodo tener que ir hasta allí en auto cada vez que tenemos que enviar un paquete.",
    "answer": "inconvenient, uneasy, cumbersome",
    "answerDetails": "It is inconvenient to drive there every time we need to send a large package."
  },
  {
    "id": 4815,
    "question": "novedades",
    "questionDetails": "Todos sus favoritos y una o dos novedades.",
    "answer": "novelties, news, developments",
    "answerDetails": "All your favourites and one or two novelties."
  },
  {
    "id": 4816,
    "question": "quédense",
    "questionDetails": "Quédense en su lugar.",
    "answer": "stay, stick around",
    "answerDetails": "Stay where you belong."
  },
  {
    "id": 4817,
    "question": "garantizo",
    "questionDetails": "Le garantizo que el plan del almirante es bueno.",
    "answer": "guarantee, assure",
    "answerDetails": "I guarantee the admiral’s plan is sound."
  },
  {
    "id": 4818,
    "question": "serios",
    "questionDetails": "Si realmente somos serios y nos preocupa.",
    "answer": "serious",
    "answerDetails": "And if we are at all serious and are concerned."
  },
  {
    "id": 4819,
    "question": "díselo",
    "questionDetails": "Díselo al juez entonces.",
    "answer": "tell",
    "answerDetails": "Tell the judge that."
  },
  {
    "id": 4820,
    "question": "evitarlo",
    "questionDetails": "Realmente deseaba evitarlo esta vez.",
    "answer": "avoid",
    "answerDetails": "I was really hoping to avoid that this time."
  },
  {
    "id": 4821,
    "question": "fiar",
    "questionDetails": "… hacer desaparecer millones, y luego parecer fiar días después.",
    "answer": "legit, trust, reliable",
    "answerDetails": "… make millions disappear, then look legit days later."
  },
  {
    "id": 4822,
    "question": "roma",
    "questionDetails": "Aunque Roma es famosa por ser la capital de Italia, prefiero Venecia.",
    "answer": "rome",
    "answerDetails": "Although Rome is famous for being the capital of Italy, I much prefer Venice."
  },
  {
    "id": 4823,
    "question": "terminen",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando terminen, tomen sus lugares.",
    "answer": "finish",
    "answerDetails": "When you finish, take your place over there."
  },
  {
    "id": 4824,
    "question": "armada",
    "questionDetails": "Se unió a la Armada en 1990.",
    "answer": "navy",
    "answerDetails": "She joined the Navy in 1990."
  },
  {
    "id": 4825,
    "question": "comentó",
    "questionDetails": "Me comentó que ese espectro se …",
    "answer": "commented, remarked, said",
    "answerDetails": "I commented, as that spectre …"
  },
  {
    "id": 4826,
    "question": "retirarse",
    "questionDetails": "La falta de números obligó a la fuerza británica a retirarse.",
    "answer": "retire, retreat",
    "answerDetails": "Lack of numbers compelled the British force to retire."
  },
  {
    "id": 4827,
    "question": "vuela",
    "questionDetails": "Pero esto vuela más eficazmente que esto.",
    "answer": "flies, blow, soar",
    "answerDetails": "But this flies better than that."
  },
  {
    "id": 4828,
    "question": "tomarse",
    "questionDetails": "Podría tomarse el día libre.",
    "answer": "take",
    "answerDetails": "Might take the day off!"
  },
  {
    "id": 4829,
    "question": "protagonista",
    "questionDetails": "El protagonista principal de la novela es un oficial de inteligencia estadounidense.",
    "answer": "protagonist",
    "answerDetails": "The novel’s main protagonist is an American intelligence officer."
  },
  {
    "id": 4830,
    "question": "trabajador",
    "questionDetails": "Usted no es un trabajador ferroviario.",
    "answer": "worker",
    "answerDetails": "You are nota railway worker."
  },
  {
    "id": 4831,
    "question": "intervenir",
    "questionDetails": "Si los grandes poderes querían intervenir.",
    "answer": "intervene",
    "answerDetails": "If the great powers wanted to intervene."
  },
  {
    "id": 4832,
    "question": "tocan",
    "questionDetails": "Mis manos te tocan, mis ojos te ven.",
    "answer": "touch",
    "answerDetails": "My hands touch you, my eyes see you."
  },
  {
    "id": 4833,
    "question": "temporal",
    "questionDetails": "Me dieron una visa temporal para entrar a los Estados Unidos.",
    "answer": "temporary",
    "answerDetails": "I was granted a temporary visa to enter the United States."
  },
  {
    "id": 4834,
    "question": "unir",
    "questionDetails": "Llamó al partido para unir.",
    "answer": "unite, bind",
    "answerDetails": "He called on the party to unite."
  },
  {
    "id": 4835,
    "question": "baños",
    "questionDetails": "Una visita a los baños turcos seguramente será una experiencia reconstituyente.",
    "answer": "baths",
    "answerDetails": "A visit to the Turkish baths is sure to be a restorative experience."
  },
  {
    "id": 4836,
    "question": "explicarme",
    "questionDetails": "Nada podría explicarme esto.",
    "answer": "explain",
    "answerDetails": "Nothing could explain this."
  },
  {
    "id": 4837,
    "question": "tomarte",
    "questionDetails": "Deberías tomarte unos días.",
    "answer": "take",
    "answerDetails": "You should take some time off."
  },
  {
    "id": 4838,
    "question": "avisaron",
    "answer": "Told"
  },
  {
    "id": 4839,
    "question": "internacionales",
    "questionDetails": "Entrar como trabajadores voluntarios internacionales.",
    "answer": "international",
    "answerDetails": "Going in as international aid workers."
  },
  {
    "id": 4840,
    "question": "complejo",
    "questionDetails": "Se estrenará el complejo médico más moderno del país en Enero.",
    "answer": "center",
    "answerDetails": "The country’s most modern medical center will open in January."
  },
  {
    "id": 4841,
    "question": "pájaro",
    "questionDetails": "Las urracas son algunos de los pájaros más inteligentes.",
    "answer": "bird",
    "answerDetails": "Magpies are among the most intelligent of birds."
  },
  {
    "id": 4842,
    "question": "conocías",
    "questionDetails": "Conocías a muchos cubanos cuando vivías en Miami, ¿cierto?",
    "answer": "you knew",
    "answerDetails": "You knew a lot of Cubans when you lived in Miami, right?"
  },
  {
    "id": 4843,
    "question": "actuación",
    "questionDetails": "Después de la cuarta derrota seguida, los fanáticos comenzaron a quejarse sobre la actuación del equipo.",
    "answer": "performance, action, gig",
    "answerDetails": "After the fourth loss in a row, fans began to complain about the team’s performance."
  },
  {
    "id": 4844,
    "question": "cerramos",
    "questionDetails": "Cerramos la bomba de vacío.",
    "answer": "close",
    "answerDetails": "Close the vacuum pump."
  },
  {
    "id": 4845,
    "question": "tapar",
    "questionDetails": "Aumentan el precio del tabaco siempre que necesitan tapar un agujero en los ingresos fiscales.",
    "answer": "plug",
    "answerDetails": "They increase tobacco duties whenever they need to plug a gap in national tax."
  },
  {
    "id": 4846,
    "question": "bebida",
    "questionDetails": "Una fiesta no es una fiesta sin bebida.",
    "answer": "drink, booze",
    "answerDetails": "A party isn’t a party without drinks."
  },
  {
    "id": 4847,
    "question": "enseñé",
    "questionDetails": "Le enseñé eso hoy.",
    "answer": "taught, showed",
    "answerDetails": "I just taught him that today."
  },
  {
    "id": 4848,
    "question": "ganan",
    "answer": "Win"
  },
  {
    "id": 4849,
    "question": "asegura",
    "questionDetails": "Eso solo asegura su supervivencia.",
    "answer": "ensures, assures, secures",
    "answerDetails": "That alone ensures your survival."
  },
  {
    "id": 4850,
    "question": "cierren",
    "questionDetails": "Si podemos meter a alguien antes de que cierren.",
    "answer": "close, shut, shut down",
    "answerDetails": "If we can get someone inside before they close it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4851,
    "question": "fallado",
    "questionDetails": "Todos los esfuerzos por contener el núcleo han fallado.",
    "answer": "failed, missed, ruled",
    "answerDetails": "All attempts to contain the core have failed."
  },
  {
    "id": 4852,
    "question": "elegí",
    "questionDetails": "Nadie me obligó: yo elegí ofrecerme como voluntaria para esta tarea.",
    "answer": "i chose",
    "answerDetails": "Nobody forced me: I chose to volunteer for this task."
  },
  {
    "id": 4853,
    "question": "dedicado",
    "questionDetails": "Siempre ha sido un estudiante dedicado, así que fue raro verlo en el pub un martes por la tarde.",
    "answer": "dedicated",
    "answerDetails": "He has always been a dedicated student, so it was odd seeing him at the pub on a Tuesday afternoon."
  },
  {
    "id": 4854,
    "question": "enseñe",
    "answer": "i taught"
  },
  {
    "id": 4855,
    "question": "árboles",
    "questionDetails": "Los árboles, el agua.",
    "answer": "trees, axles",
    "answerDetails": "Trees and the water."
  },
  {
    "id": 4856,
    "question": "cerrando",
    "questionDetails": "Algo la está cerrando desde afuera.",
    "answer": "closing, shutting, shutting down",
    "answerDetails": "Something is closing it from outside."
  },
  {
    "id": 4857,
    "question": "guantes",
    "questionDetails": "Me gustan los guantes.",
    "answer": "gloves, mittens",
    "answerDetails": "I like the gloves."
  },
  {
    "id": 4858,
    "question": "perdidos",
    "questionDetails": "Los encontramos vagando como niños perdidos.",
    "answer": "lost, missing, stray",
    "answerDetails": "We find them wandering like lost children."
  },
  {
    "id": 4859,
    "question": "escuchaba",
    "questionDetails": "El hombre escuchaba y todo se hacía realidad.",
    "answer": "listened, sounded",
    "answerDetails": "Man listened and it became real."
  },
  {
    "id": 4860,
    "question": "cigarro",
    "questionDetails": "Creo que tiene un cabo de cigarro dentro.",
    "answer": "cigar",
    "answerDetails": "I think it has a place of cigar inside."
  },
  {
    "id": 4861,
    "question": "bobo",
    "questionDetails": "¡ No seas bobo! ¡ Sabes muy bien de lo que estoy hablando!.",
    "answer": "daft",
    "answerDetails": "Don’t be daft! You know exactly what I’m talking about!."
  },
  {
    "id": 4862,
    "question": "agentes",
    "questionDetails": "Latidos detectados para todos los agentes de réplica en ejecución.",
    "answer": "agents, actors, officers",
    "answerDetails": "Heartbeats detected for all running replication agents."
  },
  {
    "id": 4863,
    "question": "pastel",
    "questionDetails": "Un pastel de boda.",
    "answer": "cake, pie",
    "answerDetails": "A wedding cake."
  },
  {
    "id": 4864,
    "question": "muévete",
    "questionDetails": "Muévete lentamente a esa esquina.",
    "answer": "move",
    "answerDetails": "Move slowly to that corner."
  },
  {
    "id": 4865,
    "question": "maricón",
    "questionDetails": "Le dijo maricón a su compañero y lo expulsaron de la escuela.",
    "answer": "faggot, poof",
    "answerDetails": "She called a classmate a faggot and was expelled from school."
  },
  {
    "id": 4866,
    "question": "computadora",
    "questionDetails": "Esos cables están probablemente conectados a la computadora.",
    "answer": "computer",
    "answerDetails": "Those cables are probably connected to the computer."
  },
  {
    "id": 4867,
    "question": "cruzados",
    "questionDetails": "así que obviamente no necesitamos cruzados",
    "answer": "crusaders, cross, folded",
    "answerDetails": "so obviously we don’t need crusaders"
  },
  {
    "id": 4868,
    "question": "londres",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "id": 4869,
    "question": "corra",
    "questionDetails": "Jamás corra con buenas noticias en el terreno.",
    "answer": "run",
    "answerDetails": "Never run good news into the ground."
  },
  {
    "id": 4870,
    "question": "ricas",
    "answer": "rich, wealthy"
  },
  {
    "id": 4871,
    "question": "coja",
    "answer": "Take"
  },
  {
    "id": 4872,
    "question": "secuestrado",
    "questionDetails": "Creemos que la han secuestrado.",
    "answer": "kidnapped, abducted, hijacked",
    "answerDetails": "We believe, she has been kidnapped."
  },
  {
    "id": 4873,
    "question": "micrófono",
    "questionDetails": "Por favor hable directamente en el micrófono. Nadie lo puede oír.",
    "answer": "mike",
    "answerDetails": "Please speak directly into the mike. No one can hear you."
  },
  {
    "id": 4874,
    "question": "protegiendo",
    "questionDetails": "Estaban protegiendo su lugar más vital.",
    "answer": "protecting, guarding",
    "answerDetails": "They were protecting their most vital spot."
  },
  {
    "id": 4875,
    "question": "metidos",
    "questionDetails": "Son todos mis extremos metidos en?",
    "answer": "tucked, involved",
    "answerDetails": "Are all my ends tucked in?"
  },
  {
    "id": 4876,
    "question": "comisaría",
    "questionDetails": "Ellos nos llevaron a la comisaría de policía.",
    "answer": "police station, precinct",
    "answerDetails": "They took us to the police station."
  },
  {
    "id": 4877,
    "question": "cogió",
    "questionDetails": "Ana dejó la trompeta y entonces cogió el micrófono y empezó a cantar.",
    "answer": "she took",
    "answerDetails": "Ana put down the trumpet, and then she took the microphone and began to sing."
  },
  {
    "id": 4878,
    "question": "lavado",
    "questionDetails": "Él no es feliz, pero él me asegura que todo va a salir en el lavado.",
    "answer": "wash, laundry",
    "answerDetails": "He’s not happy but he assures me it’ll all come out in the wash."
  },
  {
    "id": 4879,
    "question": "respondo",
    "questionDetails": "Pero también respondo a los silbidos.",
    "answer": "answer, respond, vouch",
    "answerDetails": "I also answer to whistles."
  },
  {
    "id": 4880,
    "question": "sabéis",
    "questionDetails": "Ya sabéis lo que opina vuestra madre.",
    "answer": "know",
    "answerDetails": "You know how your mother feels about that."
  },
  {
    "id": 4881,
    "question": "logro",
    "questionDetails": "El logro del reconocimiento profesional.",
    "answer": "achievement, attainment, accomplishment",
    "answerDetails": "The achievement of professional recognition."
  },
  {
    "id": 4882,
    "question": "escritorio",
    "questionDetails": "Siempre tiene bien ordenado su escritorio.",
    "answer": "desk",
    "answerDetails": "Her desk is always really organized."
  },
  {
    "id": 4883,
    "question": "varón",
    "questionDetails": "¿El bebé es varón o hembra?",
    "answer": "male",
    "answerDetails": "Is the baby male or female?"
  },
  {
    "id": 4884,
    "question": "archivos",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo acceso legal a esos archivos.",
    "answer": "files, archives, records",
    "answerDetails": "I have legal access to those files."
  },
  {
    "id": 4885,
    "question": "busquen",
    "questionDetails": "Busquen a gente que sepa.",
    "answer": "seek",
    "answerDetails": "Seek out people who know."
  },
  {
    "id": 4886,
    "question": "leyenda",
    "questionDetails": "Jesse Owens se convirtió en leyenda cuando ganó su primera medalla de Oro.",
    "answer": "legend, caption",
    "answerDetails": "Jesse Owens became a legend when he won his first gold medal."
  },
  {
    "id": 4887,
    "question": "preocupo",
    "questionDetails": "Me preocupo por ustedes.",
    "answer": "worry, worried, ‘m worried about",
    "answerDetails": "I worry for you."
  },
  {
    "id": 4888,
    "question": "acusar",
    "questionDetails": "Las autoridades de los Estados Unidos lo acusaron de espionaje.",
    "answer": "indict",
    "answerDetails": "The U.S. authorities indicted him on charges of espionage."
  },
  {
    "id": 4889,
    "question": "recupere",
    "questionDetails": "El doctor teme que no se recupere.",
    "answer": "recover, retrieve, regain",
    "answerDetails": "The doctor’s afraid that he might not even recover."
  },
  {
    "id": 4890,
    "question": "amistades",
    "questionDetails": "Invité a algunas amistades a cenar.",
    "answer": "friends",
    "answerDetails": "I invited some friends for dinner."
  },
  {
    "id": 4891,
    "question": "puros",
    "questionDetails": "Animales salvajes con verdaderos dones y talentos puros.",
    "answer": "pure, cigars",
    "answerDetails": "Wild animals with true natures and pure talents."
  },
  {
    "id": 4892,
    "question": "únicamente",
    "questionDetails": "Este año Delia ha decidido centrarse únicamente en la escritura de su novela.",
    "answer": "solely",
    "answerDetails": "Delia has decided to focus solely on the writing of her novel this year."
  },
  {
    "id": 4893,
    "question": "equivocas",
    "questionDetails": "Hoy he probado que te equivocas, madre.",
    "answer": "wrong",
    "answerDetails": "I proved you wrong today, mother."
  },
  {
    "id": 4894,
    "question": "rubia",
    "questionDetails": "La rubia con el pecho falso.",
    "answer": "blonde, blondie",
    "answerDetails": "The blonde with the false chest?"
  },
  {
    "id": 4895,
    "question": "aparato",
    "questionDetails": "El aparato de la ciencia podría aumentar los rendimientos de los cultivos.",
    "answer": "appliance, apparatus, equipment",
    "answerDetails": "The appliance of science could increase crop yields."
  },
  {
    "id": 4896,
    "question": "intimidad",
    "questionDetails": "La comunicación es muy importante para lograr intimidad en una relación o amistad.",
    "answer": "intimacy",
    "answerDetails": "Communication is really important to achieve intimacy in a relationship or friendship."
  },
  {
    "id": 4897,
    "question": "bandeja",
    "questionDetails": "Trae la bandeja y así desayunamos en la cama.",
    "answer": "tray",
    "answerDetails": "Bring the tray here and let’s have breakfast in bed."
  },
  {
    "id": 4898,
    "question": "comunicado",
    "questionDetails": "El gobierno publicó un comunicado para condenar las manifestaciones recientes.",
    "answer": "release, connected, statement",
    "answerDetails": "The government issued a release condemning the recent riots."
  },
  {
    "id": 4899,
    "question": "empleo",
    "questionDetails": "No tener empleo, estar desempleado (a) Or.",
    "answer": "employment, job",
    "answerDetails": "To be without employment."
  },
  {
    "id": 4900,
    "question": "chistes",
    "answer": "joking"
  },
  {
    "id": 4901,
    "question": "aprovecho",
    "questionDetails": "Aprovecho la ocasión para dar …",
    "answer": "take",
    "answerDetails": "I should like to take the opportunity here to give …"
  },
  {
    "id": 4902,
    "question": "fingir",
    "questionDetails": "Desde que salí del armario, ya no tengo que fingir.",
    "answer": "pretend",
    "answerDetails": "Since I came out of the closet, I don’t have to pretend anymore."
  },
  {
    "id": 4903,
    "question": "localizar",
    "questionDetails": "Los detectives están tratando de localizar el automóvil del sospechoso.",
    "answer": "trace",
    "answerDetails": "Detectives are trying to trace the car of the suspect."
  },
  {
    "id": 4904,
    "question": "dormí",
    "answer": "Slept"
  },
  {
    "id": 4905,
    "question": "mantenga",
    "questionDetails": "Dile que mantenga la línea abierta.",
    "answer": "keep, maintain, hold",
    "answerDetails": "Tell him to keep the line open."
  },
  {
    "id": 4906,
    "question": "tocas",
    "questionDetails": "Quisiera que me tocas es por todas partes.",
    "answer": "touch",
    "answerDetails": "I want you to touch me all over."
  },
  {
    "id": 4907,
    "question": "duela",
    "answer": "stave"
  },
  {
    "id": 4908,
    "question": "permanecer",
    "questionDetails": "Creo que es mejor permanecer cerca de la carretera.",
    "answer": "stay",
    "answerDetails": "I think it is better to stay close and road."
  },
  {
    "id": 4909,
    "question": "cállense",
    "questionDetails": "Cállense los dos y sigan buscando.",
    "answer": "shut up",
    "answerDetails": "Both of you shut up and keep looking."
  },
  {
    "id": 4910,
    "question": "simpático",
    "questionDetails": "Habló en un tono simpático.",
    "answer": "sympathetic, likeable, endearing",
    "answerDetails": "He spoke in a sympathetic tone."
  },
  {
    "id": 4911,
    "question": "hacéis",
    "questionDetails": "Sabéis lo que hacéis.",
    "answer": "do",
    "answerDetails": "You know what you do."
  },
  {
    "id": 4912,
    "question": "profundamente",
    "questionDetails": "Encendió un cigarrillo e inhaló profundamente.",
    "answer": "deeply, profoundly, soundly",
    "answerDetails": "She lit a cigarette and inhaled deeply."
  },
  {
    "id": 4913,
    "question": "perseguir",
    "questionDetails": "Perseguir ese sentimiento inicial que nunca lo recupera ras.",
    "answer": "pursue",
    "answerDetails": "To pursue that feeling initial that you never recovered it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4914,
    "question": "traten",
    "questionDetails": "Traten de rastrear mi señal.",
    "answer": "try, treat",
    "answerDetails": "Try and home in on my signal."
  },
  {
    "id": 4915,
    "question": "conjunto",
    "questionDetails": "Tuvimos que encontrar el conjunto de los números primos positivos de menos de 100.",
    "answer": "set, whole, group",
    "answerDetails": "We had to find the set of positive prime numbers less than 100."
  },
  {
    "id": 4916,
    "question": "pasemos",
    "questionDetails": "Pero será mejor que pasemos la noche aquí.",
    "answer": "spend",
    "answerDetails": "But we better spend the night."
  },
  {
    "id": 4917,
    "question": "manden",
    "questionDetails": "Mejor antes manden una postal.",
    "answer": "send",
    "answerDetails": "Best send a postcard first."
  },
  {
    "id": 4918,
    "question": "hablaré",
    "questionDetails": "Hablaré contigo cuando termine mi reunión.",
    "answer": "i will speak, i will talk",
    "answerDetails": "I will speak with you when my meeting is over."
  },
  {
    "id": 4919,
    "question": "empiecen",
    "questionDetails": "Empiecen con los oficiales y vayan bajando en rango.",
    "answer": "start, begin",
    "answerDetails": "Start with the officers and work your way down."
  },
  {
    "id": 4920,
    "question": "encanto",
    "questionDetails": "Antes de que pudiera encender el encanto, que colgaban.",
    "answer": "charm, allure, enchantment",
    "answerDetails": "Before I could turn on the charm, they hung up."
  },
  {
    "id": 4921,
    "question": "levantó",
    "answer": "he built"
  },
  {
    "id": 4922,
    "question": "fáciles",
    "questionDetails": "Fuimos fáciles de hacer.",
    "answer": "easy, easily",
    "answerDetails": "We was easy to make."
  },
  {
    "id": 4923,
    "question": "sábanas",
    "questionDetails": "¿Puedes quitar las sábanas y ponerlas en el cesto de la ropa sucia?",
    "answer": "bedding",
    "answerDetails": "Can you strip off the bedding and put it in the laundry hamper?"
  },
  {
    "id": 4924,
    "question": "velas",
    "questionDetails": "Por una vez, velas en casa.",
    "answer": "candles, sails",
    "answerDetails": "Candles at home, for once."
  },
  {
    "id": 4925,
    "question": "productos",
    "answer": "truck"
  },
  {
    "id": 4926,
    "question": "bicho",
    "questionDetails": "Ese bicho me friquea.",
    "answer": "weirdo, critter",
    "answerDetails": "That weirdo freaks me out."
  },
  {
    "id": 4927,
    "question": "prestado",
    "questionDetails": "No peleemos por el dinero prestado. Te daré otra semana.",
    "answer": "borrowed",
    "answerDetails": "Let’s not fight over the borrowed money. I will give you another week."
  },
  {
    "id": 4928,
    "question": "mueven",
    "questionDetails": "Las señales mueven las cosas arriba y abajo.",
    "answer": "move",
    "answerDetails": "Signals move things up and down."
  },
  {
    "id": 4929,
    "question": "mudo",
    "questionDetails": "Un mudo increiblemente fuerte.",
    "answer": "mute, dumb, speechless",
    "answerDetails": "An incredibly big mute."
  },
  {
    "id": 4930,
    "question": "acceder",
    "questionDetails": "El veneno para ratas se debe colocar en un lugar donde no lo pueden acceder las mascotas.",
    "answer": "get at",
    "answerDetails": "The rat poison should be placed somewhere where pets can’t get at it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4931,
    "question": "salve",
    "questionDetails": "Todos los soldados de la legión gritaron: “¡ Salve, Emperador!”.",
    "answer": "hail",
    "answerDetails": "Every soldier of the legion cried: “Hail, Emperor!”."
  },
  {
    "id": 4932,
    "question": "infantil",
    "questionDetails": "El Partido Laborista Infantil.",
    "answer": "infant",
    "answerDetails": "The infant Labour Party."
  },
  {
    "id": 4933,
    "question": "separado",
    "questionDetails": "Su madre y su padre están separados.",
    "answer": "separate, apart",
    "answerDetails": "Her mother and father are separated."
  },
  {
    "id": 4934,
    "question": "limpiando",
    "questionDetails": "Uno de ustedes debe haber estado limpiando.",
    "answer": "cleaning, wiping, swabbing",
    "answerDetails": "One of you must have been cleaning."
  },
  {
    "id": 4935,
    "question": "escribo",
    "questionDetails": "Yo escribo un poco.",
    "answer": "write",
    "answerDetails": "I write a bit."
  },
  {
    "id": 4936,
    "question": "diciembre",
    "answer": "December"
  },
  {
    "id": 4937,
    "question": "implica",
    "answer": "it involves"
  },
  {
    "id": 4938,
    "question": "encontrarse",
    "questionDetails": "Los 2 yates zarparon y acordaron encontrarse 3 semanas más tarde en Ciudad del Cabo.",
    "answer": "rendezvous",
    "answerDetails": "The two yachts left port and arranged to rendezvous three weeks later in Cape Town."
  },
  {
    "id": 4939,
    "question": "ríe",
    "answer": "Laugh"
  },
  {
    "id": 4940,
    "question": "crecido",
    "answer": "tall"
  },
  {
    "id": 4941,
    "question": "envía",
    "questionDetails": "Le envía sus disculpas.",
    "answer": "sends, shipped, dispatches",
    "answerDetails": "He sends his apologies."
  },
  {
    "id": 4942,
    "question": "emocional",
    "questionDetails": "Él era un hombre joven fuertemente emocional.",
    "answer": "emotional",
    "answerDetails": "He was a strongly emotional young man."
  },
  {
    "id": 4943,
    "question": "impulso",
    "questionDetails": "Todos perdimos el impulso de trabajar en el proyecto después de que oímos los comentarios despreciativos de nuestro jefe.",
    "answer": "momentum, boost, impetus",
    "answerDetails": "We all lost our momentum to work on the project after we heard our boss’s disparaging remarks."
  },
  {
    "id": 4944,
    "question": "mérito",
    "questionDetails": "El cabello corto no indica ningún mérito.",
    "answer": "merit",
    "answerDetails": "Short hair is no indication of merit."
  },
  {
    "id": 4945,
    "question": "expresión",
    "answer": "utterance"
  },
  {
    "id": 4946,
    "question": "notado",
    "questionDetails": "Incluso los niños lo han notado.",
    "answer": "noticed",
    "answerDetails": "Even the kids have noticed."
  },
  {
    "id": 4947,
    "question": "tuvieran",
    "questionDetails": "Como si nuestros granos de café tuvieran pedigrí.",
    "answer": "had",
    "answerDetails": "As if every bean in our coffee had a pedigree."
  },
  {
    "id": 4948,
    "question": "jornada",
    "questionDetails": "La jornada comenzó con una presentación.",
    "answer": "day",
    "answerDetails": "The day began with an introduction."
  },
  {
    "id": 4949,
    "question": "hijita",
    "questionDetails": "Y ahora, mi hijita está enferma.",
    "answer": "little girl",
    "answerDetails": "And now my little girl is sick."
  },
  {
    "id": 4950,
    "question": "andá",
    "questionDetails": "Andá a dormir entonces.",
    "answer": "go",
    "answerDetails": "Go to sleep then."
  },
  {
    "id": 4951,
    "question": "fiscalía",
    "questionDetails": "La fiscalía tiene todavía un testigo.",
    "answer": "prosecution, procuracy, prosecutorial",
    "answerDetails": "Prosecution has another witness."
  },
  {
    "id": 4952,
    "question": "suélteme",
    "answer": "let me go"
  },
  {
    "id": 4953,
    "question": "nene",
    "questionDetails": "Lo hago todo por ti, nene.",
    "answer": "baby",
    "answerDetails": "I do everything for you, baby."
  },
  {
    "id": 4954,
    "question": "óyeme",
    "questionDetails": "Óyeme podríamos llevar a este …",
    "answer": "listen",
    "answerDetails": "Listen we could get this …"
  },
  {
    "id": 4955,
    "question": "you",
    "questionDetails": "I’ll Order After you.",
    "answer": "ti, os",
    "answerDetails": "Yo pediré después de ti."
  },
  {
    "id": 4956,
    "question": "sincera",
    "questionDetails": "Se que eres sincera y bien intencionada.",
    "answer": "sincere, honest, heartfelt",
    "answerDetails": "You that you are sincere and very deliberate."
  },
  {
    "id": 4957,
    "question": "regresamos",
    "questionDetails": "Después del concierto, regresamos a mi casa.",
    "answer": "we returned",
    "answerDetails": "After the concert, we returned to my house."
  },
  {
    "id": 4958,
    "question": "tragos",
    "questionDetails": "Me detuve en el camino por un par de tragos.",
    "answer": "drinks, swigs, gulps",
    "answerDetails": "I stopped along the way for a couple of drinks."
  },
  {
    "id": 4959,
    "question": "liberar",
    "questionDetails": "El rey ha proclamado que liberará a todos los prisioneros de guerra.",
    "answer": "release, liberate, unlock",
    "answerDetails": "The King has proclaimed that he will release all prisoners of war."
  },
  {
    "id": 4960,
    "question": "vuestro",
    "questionDetails": "Este es vuestro momento.",
    "answer": "your",
    "answerDetails": "This is your moment."
  },
  {
    "id": 4961,
    "question": "celulares",
    "questionDetails": "Extraen nuestros péptidos celulares.",
    "answer": "cellular, cell, phones",
    "answerDetails": "They extract our cellular peptides."
  },
  {
    "id": 4962,
    "question": "ordenó",
    "questionDetails": "Le ordenó al mesero a limpiar la mesa.",
    "answer": "he told",
    "answerDetails": "He told the waiter to clean up the table."
  },
  {
    "id": 4963,
    "question": "seguís",
    "questionDetails": "O me lleváis con vosotros o me seguís allí.",
    "answer": "follow",
    "answerDetails": "Either take me with you or follow me there."
  },
  {
    "id": 4964,
    "question": "investigaciones",
    "questionDetails": "Hay que llevar a cabo más investigaciones sobre la influencia de los medios sociales en nuestras vidas.",
    "answer": "research",
    "answerDetails": "We need to carry out more research on the influence of social media on our lives."
  },
  {
    "id": 4965,
    "question": "cometí",
    "questionDetails": "Quizás cometí un error con las columnas.",
    "answer": "made",
    "answerDetails": "Maybe made a mistake with the columns."
  },
  {
    "id": 4966,
    "question": "acusando",
    "questionDetails": "No estamos acusando a nadie.",
    "answer": "accusing",
    "answerDetails": "We are not accusing anyone."
  },
  {
    "id": 4967,
    "question": "horribles",
    "questionDetails": "Me sigo acordando de cosas buenas en lugar de horribles.",
    "answer": "horrible, awful, hideous",
    "answerDetails": "I keep thinking of nice things instead of horrible ones."
  },
  {
    "id": 4968,
    "question": "encargue",
    "questionDetails": "Deja que alguien más se encargue.",
    "answer": "handle",
    "answerDetails": "Let someone else handle it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4969,
    "question": "agarran",
    "questionDetails": "pero ellos agarran a la presa y comienzan a hacerla girar …",
    "answer": "seize",
    "answerDetails": "but they seize it and start spinning …"
  },
  {
    "id": 4970,
    "question": "lastimar",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca lastimaría a un hombre indefenso.",
    "answer": "harm",
    "answerDetails": "I would never harm an unarmed man."
  },
  {
    "id": 4971,
    "question": "meterle",
    "questionDetails": "Meterle ese radio por la cabeza.",
    "answer": "shove, put",
    "answerDetails": "Shove that radio right through the side of his head."
  },
  {
    "id": 4972,
    "question": "borracha",
    "questionDetails": "Yo estaba muy borracha.",
    "answer": "drunk, drunken, lush",
    "answerDetails": "I was so drunk."
  },
  {
    "id": 4973,
    "question": "imbéciles",
    "questionDetails": "Imbéciles morales ante el hombre común.",
    "answer": "imbeciles, jerks, idiots",
    "answerDetails": "Moral imbeciles to a man."
  },
  {
    "id": 4974,
    "question": "beneficios",
    "questionDetails": "La empresa cuestiona si podrá sostener el crecimiento de beneficios con 1$ más fuerte.",
    "answer": "earnings, gains",
    "answerDetails": "The company questions whether it will be able to retain its earnings growth with a stronger dollar."
  },
  {
    "id": 4975,
    "question": "impuestos",
    "questionDetails": "Los impuestos son un hecho.",
    "answer": "taxes, taxation, imposed",
    "answerDetails": "Taxes are a fact."
  },
  {
    "id": 4976,
    "question": "cuenten",
    "questionDetails": "Y ciertamente cuenten con mi apoyo.",
    "answer": "count",
    "answerDetails": "And indeed count on my support."
  },
  {
    "id": 4977,
    "question": "patrulla",
    "questionDetails": "Romper a los cachorros en seises y Scouts en patrullas.",
    "answer": "patrol",
    "answerDetails": "Break the Cubs into sixes and Scouts into patrols."
  },
  {
    "id": 4978,
    "question": "defenderme",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo derecho a defenderme.",
    "answer": "defend myself",
    "answerDetails": "I have a right to defend myself."
  },
  {
    "id": 4979,
    "question": "torta",
    "questionDetails": "Usted no ha recibido una porción justa de la torta de la educación.",
    "answer": "cake",
    "answerDetails": "You have not received a fair slice of the education cake."
  },
  {
    "id": 4980,
    "question": "legales",
    "questionDetails": "Los derechos legales de la investigación son claros.",
    "answer": "legal, statutory, lawful",
    "answerDetails": "The legal investigation rights are clear."
  },
  {
    "id": 4981,
    "question": "arregle",
    "questionDetails": "Puede que arregle relojes también.",
    "answer": "fix, straightened out",
    "answerDetails": "He might fix clocks, too."
  },
  {
    "id": 4982,
    "question": "confesión",
    "questionDetails": "La confesión del ladrón finalmente puso fin a la investigación.",
    "answer": "admission, confession",
    "answerDetails": "The thief’s admission finally brought the investigation to a close."
  },
  {
    "id": 4983,
    "question": "lotería",
    "questionDetails": "Se sacó la lotería.",
    "answer": "jackpot",
    "answerDetails": "She really hit the jackpot."
  },
  {
    "id": 4984,
    "question": "regala",
    "questionDetails": "Así que regala los dólares.",
    "answer": "gives",
    "answerDetails": "So it gives the dollars away."
  },
  {
    "id": 4985,
    "question": "vivas",
    "questionDetails": "Me preocupa tanto que vivas sola.",
    "answer": "living, alive, vivid",
    "answerDetails": "I worry so about you living alone."
  },
  {
    "id": 4986,
    "question": "relajado",
    "questionDetails": "Hace dos segundos estaba relajado.",
    "answer": "relaxed",
    "answerDetails": "I was relaxed about two seconds ago."
  },
  {
    "id": 4987,
    "question": "prometer",
    "questionDetails": "Ella me hizo prometer no decírselo a nadie.",
    "answer": "promise",
    "answerDetails": "She made me promise not to tell a soul."
  },
  {
    "id": 4988,
    "question": "psicólogo",
    "questionDetails": "Éste es el número de mi psicólogo.",
    "answer": "psychologist",
    "answerDetails": "This is the number of my psychologist."
  },
  {
    "id": 4989,
    "question": "alcanzó",
    "answer": "Reached"
  },
  {
    "id": 4990,
    "question": "agarrado",
    "questionDetails": "Ruy se corta el pelo él mismo y se niega a ir a un barbero porque es agarrado.",
    "answer": "tightfisted",
    "answerDetails": "Ruy cuts his own hair and refuses to see a barber because he is tightfisted."
  },
  {
    "id": 4991,
    "question": "espiando",
    "questionDetails": "Alguien estuvo espiando el juego de cartas.",
    "answer": "spying on, spying, peeping",
    "answerDetails": "Someone was spying on the card game."
  },
  {
    "id": 4992,
    "question": "tomarnos",
    "questionDetails": "Creo que todos deberíamos tomarnos un descanso ahora.",
    "answer": "take",
    "answerDetails": "I think maybe everyone should take a break now."
  },
  {
    "id": 4993,
    "question": "cambias",
    "questionDetails": "Pero si lo único que cambias es la fecha.",
    "answer": "change",
    "answerDetails": "All you do is change the date."
  },
  {
    "id": 4994,
    "question": "interesan",
    "questionDetails": "Ni siquiera me interesan más las mujeres.",
    "answer": "interest, interested",
    "answerDetails": "Even women don’t interest me any more."
  },
  {
    "id": 4995,
    "question": "intensa",
    "questionDetails": "En un solo lugar, pero muy intensa.",
    "answer": "intense, intensely",
    "answerDetails": "It is localized, but very intense."
  },
  {
    "id": 4996,
    "question": "cambies",
    "questionDetails": "Sugiero que te cambies por algo más apropiado.",
    "answer": "change",
    "answerDetails": "I suggest you change into something more suitable."
  },
  {
    "id": 4997,
    "question": "tomate",
    "questionDetails": "Estos tomates se ven deliciosos.",
    "answer": "tomato",
    "answerDetails": "These tomatoes look delicious."
  },
  {
    "id": 4998,
    "question": "entiendan",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que esos convictos entiendan quién manda.",
    "answer": "understand",
    "answerDetails": "I want those cons to understand who owns them."
  },
  {
    "id": 4999,
    "question": "cruel",
    "questionDetails": "Que era cruel de ella para criticar.",
    "answer": "unkind, callous",
    "answerDetails": "It was unkind of her to criticize."
  },
  {
    "id": 5000,
    "question": "abandonada",
    "questionDetails": "Una aldea abandonada, sin habitantes.",
    "answer": "abandoned, deserted, derelict",
    "answerDetails": "An abandoned village, a ghost town."
  }
]
